<records>
<rec resultID="1">
  <header shortDbName="eric" longDbName="ERIC" uiTerm="ED516677">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo>
        <isbn type="print">978-1-1097-7515-0</isbn>
      </bkinfo>
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>ProQuest LLC</jtl>
        <issn type="print">ERICRIE0</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2010" month="01" day="01">20100101</dt>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ppct>232</ppct>
        <tig>
          <atl>Information Systems, Competitive Dynamics, and Firm Performance: An Interpretive and Centering Resonance Analysis</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Vannoy, Sandra A.</au>
        </aug>
        <su>Grounded Theory</su>
        <su>Organizational Communication</su>
        <su>Industry</su>
        <su>Network Analysis</su>
        <su>Information Systems</su>
        <su>Information Technology</su>
        <su>Program Effectiveness</su>
        <su>Information Seeking</su>
        <su>Competition</su>
        <su>Influence of Technology</su>
        <su>Social Networks</su>
        <su>Computer Mediated Communication</su>
        <su>Interviews</su>
        <su>Organizational Effectiveness</su>
        <su>Knowledge Management</su>
        <su>Business Administration</su>
        <pubtype>Dissertations/Theses - Doctoral Dissertations</pubtype>
        <ab>This dissertation examines, from a managerial interpretive perspective, how information systems contribute to firms' specific competitive actions and responses, and the resultant impacts upon firm performance. The findings from this research suggest that the answer may well lie within the role of information systems in firms' competitive dynamics or the specific competitive actions and/or responses in which firms engage. This dissertation comprises two studies. Study I examines managerial interpretations of the role played by information systems in firms' competitive dynamics and firm performance. Study II examines the role of social computing and communication technologies in intrafirm social networks and digitally-mediated aggregate cognitive maps at each stage of a competitive dynamics process. The results of Study I in this dissertation suggest a process model, grounded in data from in-depth interviews with executive- and operational-level organizational managers, industry experts and from relevant organizational and industry documents. The relationships inherent in a firm's information systems, competitive dynamics and firm performance can be traced through four interrelated grounded theoretical categories--IT-enhanced Organizational Information Processing and Competitive Action, Information-driven Competitive Action Decision, Execution/Abandonment, and Firm Performance. Thus, the first study contributes to understanding how information systems enable a process of knowledge dissemination and sharing among managerial decision-makers, how information systems enable a collective and rational competitive action decision-making process, how information systems facilitate and create message channeling systems and create the platform toward competitive actions enactment, and thus, how firm performance is impacted by information systems. This study shows the way in which information systems impact firm performance through the competitive actions and reactions undertaken by a dominant firm. Dominant firms have shown the ability to attain and retain superior performance and exhibit sustained competitive advantage. Thus, the study of the role of information systems in the context of the competitive activity of a dominant firm should be of value to both academics and practitioners. The second study in this dissertation examines the role of social computing and communications technologies in intrafirm social networks and digitally-mediated aggregate cognitive maps embedded within the process of conceiving, enacting and executing firms' competitive actions and responses and resulting impacts upon firm performance. The role of information systems in this context raises important new issues that have not been addressed by current information systems research. By examining the role of internal managerial social networks formed around social computing and communications technologies that are used in the conception, enactment and execution of firms' competitive dynamics, it is possible to unearth a more complex and integrated role of information systems in organizations. Study II builds upon the literature in the following areas of research: information systems and firm performance, competitive dynamics in the specific context of the awareness-motivation-capability perspective, social computing, social network theory, and organizational communication in the specific areas of collective and distributed cognition, information seeking and sharing, and organizational memory and learning. The combination of research methods employed in this dissertation makes a unique contribution to research in its own right. The research methodologies used in Study II are Social Network Analysis and Centering Resonance Analysis in conjunction with the Grounded Theoretical findings from Study I. Grounded Theory has been used in Study I to identify the central concepts, build theory and explain the general role of information systems in competitive actions and firm performance. In Study II, Social Network Analysis and Centering Resonance Analysis have been used to build upon Grounded Theory by examining the collective and interactive nature of organizational communication and decision-making in the context of social computing. Specifically, social relationships and organizational communication processes are examined in this research in the context of social computing and communications technologies embedded within the conception, enactment, and execution of competitive actions and responses toward impacts on firm performance. The two studies are synthesized to provide a novel perspective about a very complex and multifaceted phenomenon: understanding the impact of information systems on firm performance through the lens of competitive dynamics. Specifically, the findings from this dissertation suggest that to account for the impact of information systems upon firm performance, researchers should consider the organizational context, the intentions and actions of key players, and the process of conceiving, enacting and executing competitive actions or responses carried out by the organization. Findings also suggest that practitioners will be better able to leverage IT investments if they understand the embedded role of information systems within the competitive actions or responses undertaken by the firm to maintain or improve relative performance. (Abstract shortened by UMI.) [The dissertation citations contained here are published with the permission of ProQuest LLC. Further reproduction is prohibited without permission. Copies of dissertations may be obtained by Telephone (800) 1-800-521-0600. Web page: http://www.proquest.com/en-US/products/dissertations/individuals.shtml.]</ab>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="eng">English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=eric&amp;AN=ED516677&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="2">
  <header shortDbName="bth" longDbName="Business Source Complete" uiTerm="31999217">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Journal of Business Ethics</jtl>
        <issn>01674544</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2008" month="06" day="30">Jun2008</dt>
        <vid>80</vid>
        <iid>2</iid>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ui type="doi">10.1007/s10551-007-9417-1</ui>
        <ppf>263</ppf>
        <ppct>16</ppct>
        <formats>
          <fmt type="PDF" size="278KB" />
        </formats>
        <tig>
          <atl>Principles and Influence in Codes of Ethics: A Centering Resonance Analysis Comparing Pre- and Post-Sarbanes-Oxley Codes of Ethics.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Canary, Heather</au>
          <au>Jennings, Marianne</au>
          <affil>Humanities &amp; Arts , Arizona State University at the Polytechnic Campus , Bell Hall, 7001 E. Williams Field Road Mesa 85212 USA</affil>
          <affil>W.P. Carey School of Business , Arizona State University , Tempe USA</affil>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="thes">FINANCIAL disclosure</subj>
          <subj type="thes">BUSINESS ethics</subj>
          <subj type="thes">PROFESSIONAL ethics</subj>
          <subj type="thes">FAIR presentation</subj>
          <subj type="thes">BUSINESS enterprises</subj>
          <subj type="thes">CORPORATIONS -- Corrupt practices</subj>
          <subj type="geo">UNITED States</subj>
          <subj type="unclass">CODES of ethics</subj>
          <subj type="unclass">ETHICS</subj>
          <subj type="unclass">LAW &amp; legislation</subj>
          <subj type="unclass">UNITED States -- Politics &amp; government -- 2001-2009</subj>
          <subj type="unclass">ETHICS -- United States</subj>
          <subj type="unclass">LAW &amp; ethics</subj>
          <subj type="product">UNITED States. Sarbanes-Oxley Act of 2002</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>This study examines the similarities and differences in pre- and post-Sarbanes-Oxley corporate ethics codes and codes of conduct using the framework of structuration theory. Following the passage of the Sarbanes-Oxley (SOX) legislation in 2002 in the United States, publicly traded companies there undertook development and revision of their codes of ethics in response to new regulatory requirements as well as incentives under the U.S. Corporate Sentencing Guidelines, which were also revised as part of the SOX mandates. Questions that remain are whether these new or revised codes are effective means of communicating changed ethical foci and attitudes in organizations. Centering resonance analysis (CRA) is used to identify differences and similarities across time and industries by analyzing word networks of 46 pre- and post-SOX corporate codes of ethics. Analyses focus on content and structure of generated word networks as well as resulting factors that emerged from the texts. Results are interpreted from the structuration perspective that content and structure of codes are constrained and enabled by system structures while they function to produce and reproduce those structures. Results indicate that corporate codes of ethics are formal discourses of ethics, laws, and control. Code structure has changed across time, with an increased emphasis on compliance in post-SOX codes. Implications for research and practice are discussed in light of findings.</ab>
        <pubtype>Academic Journal</pubtype>
        <doctype>Article</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="eng">English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=bth&amp;AN=31999217&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="3">
  <header shortDbName="bth" longDbName="Business Source Complete" uiTerm="91831816">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Communications of the Association for Information Systems</jtl>
        <issn>15293181</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2013" month="09" day="01">Sep2013</dt>
        <vid>33</vid>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ppf>15</ppf>
        <ppct>18</ppct>
        <formats>
          <fmt type="PDF" size="2.3MB" />
        </formats>
        <tig>
          <atl>Uncovering Research Opportunities in the Medical Informatics Field: A Quantitative Content Analysis.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Weigel, Fred K.</au>
          <au>Rainer Jr., R. Kelly</au>
          <au>Hazen, Benjamin T.</au>
          <au>Cegielski, Casey G.</au>
          <au>Ford, F. Nelson</au>
          <affil>Army-Baylor Graduate Program in Health and Business Administration, Baylor University</affil>
          <affil>Department of Supply Chain and Information Systems Management, Auburn University</affil>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="thes">QUANTITATIVE research</subj>
          <subj type="thes">INFORMATION storage &amp; retrieval systems</subj>
          <subj type="thes">INFORMATION technology</subj>
          <subj type="unclass">MEDICAL informatics</subj>
          <subj type="unclass">MEDICAL care costs</subj>
          <subj type="unclass">CONTENT analysis (Communication)</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>With rapid improvements in technology, the ever-pressing need to reduce healthcare costs, and continuing legislation emphasizing medical reforms, the demand for research within the healthcare/information systems interface is growing. In this study, we ascertain the prevalent themes from the extant medical informatics literature in an effort to motivate research beyond the traditional domain of health information technology research so information systems scholars can better understand where their expertise might contribute to advancements in healthcare. We used a quantitative content analysis method to systematically explore 2,188 article texts from journals in medical informatics, medicine, and MIS published over a ten-year period. Texts were analyzed using centering resonance analysis and factor analysis and the following themes emerged from the literature: Analytics; Healthcare Operations and Standards (with sub-themes: Operations, Project Management, and Information Assurance); Knowledge Transfer/Communication (with sub-themes: Extending beyond the Organization, Internal to the Organization, and Patient-Provider); Perceptions and Managing Expectations of Information Technology; Advancements in Research; and Software as a Service. In this article, we discuss these themes in greater detail and offer directions for future research.</ab>
        <pubtype>Academic Journal</pubtype>
        <doctype>Article</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="eng">English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=bth&amp;AN=91831816&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="4">
  <header shortDbName="cmedm" longDbName="MEDLINE" uiTerm="19940294">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>The American Journal Of Sports Medicine</jtl>
        <jtl>Am J Sports Med</jtl>
        <issn type="Electronic">1552-3365</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2010" month="02" day="01">2010 Feb</dt>
        <vid>38</vid>
        <iid>2</iid>
        <place>United States</place>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ui type="pmid">19940294</ui>
        <ui type="doi">10.1177/0363546509347105</ui>
        <pages>375-82</pages>
        <formats />
        <tig>
          <atl>Simultaneous 3D assessment of glenohumeral shape, humeral head centering, and scapular positioning in atraumatic shoulder instability: a magnetic resonance-based in vivo analysis.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>von Eisenhart-Rothe R</au>
          <au>Mayr HO</au>
          <au>Hinterwimmer S</au>
          <au>Graichen H</au>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="major">Imaging, Three-Dimensional</subj>
          <subj type="major">Joint Instability physiopathology</subj>
          <subj type="major">Magnetic Resonance Imaging</subj>
          <subj type="major">Scapula physiology</subj>
          <subj type="major">Shoulder Joint anatomy &amp; histology</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Adult</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Female</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Humans</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Image Interpretation, Computer-Assisted</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Joint Instability diagnosis</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Male</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Young Adult</subj>
          <subj type="age">Adult: 19-44 years</subj>
          <subj type="age">Young Adult: 19-24 years</subj>
          <subj type="age">All Adult: 19+ years</subj>
          <subj type="gender">Female</subj>
          <subj type="gender">Male</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>Success rates in the treatment of atraumatic shoulder instability differ, and in vivo identification of the individual insufficient stabilizers is difficult.</ab>
        <ab>Atraumatic shoulder instability is an inhomogeneous entity with varying alterations of the active and passive stabilizers. This might be a reason for inferior treatment results.</ab>
        <ab>Case control study; Level of evidence, 3.</ab>
        <ab>Shoulders of 28 healthy volunteers and both shoulders of 14 patients with atraumatic instability and multidirectional laxity were examined in different arm positions using open magnetic resonance imaging. Three-dimensional postprocessing techniques were applied to determine 3D glenoid size and retroversion, radius of the humeral head, and curvature of the glenoid. The results of static stabilizers were compared with those of glenohumeral and scapular positioning in the same patients for identification of the individual insufficient stabilizers.</ab>
        <ab>The atraumatic unstable shoulders showed an increased mean retroversion on both sides, the difference being significant on the affected side (9.4 degrees +/- 4.8 degrees vs healthy 3.9 degrees +/- 1.3 degrees ; P &lt; .05) with a range of 2.6 degrees to 16.6 degrees . The curvature analysis demonstrated a pronounced flatness of the glenoid with a significantly increased mean radius (103.8 mm vs healthy 41.7 mm). The extent of these changes varied widely among patients. Comparison of the static stabilizers with glenohumeral and scapular positioning revealed that isolated changes of the active stabilizers exist in some patients, whereas no isolated changes of passive stabilizers were found.</ab>
        <ab>All active and passive stabilizers need to be analyzed in patients with atraumatic instability because the magnitude of alteration varied widely among individuals. Different combinations of alterations of the stabilizers were found. The presented technique allows for in vivo identification of the specific alterations. This is necessary for a better understanding of individual pathomechanics and for initiating a specific causal treatment.</ab>
        <pubtype>Journal Article</pubtype>
        <doctype>Research Support, Non-U.S. Gov't</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="eng">English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=cmedm&amp;AN=19940294&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="5">
  <header shortDbName="bth" longDbName="Business Source Complete" uiTerm="95103086">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Quality Management Journal</jtl>
        <issn>10686967</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2013" month="01" day="01">2013</dt>
        <vid>20</vid>
        <iid>1</iid>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ppf>37</ppf>
        <ppct>11</ppct>
        <formats>
          <fmt type="PDF" size="297KB" />
        </formats>
        <tig>
          <atl>A Retrospective View of Research in the Quality Management Journal: A Thematic and Keyword Analysis.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>EVANS, JAMES R.</au>
          <au>FOSTER JR., S. THOMAS</au>
          <au>ZHEN GUO</au>
          <affil>UNIVERSITY OF CINCINNATI</affil>
          <affil>BRIGHAM YOUNG UNIVERSITY</affil>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="thes">MANAGEMENT research</subj>
          <subj type="thes">TOTAL quality management</subj>
          <subj type="thes">MANAGEMENT science</subj>
          <subj type="thes">PROBLEM solving</subj>
          <subj type="unclass">KEYWORDS</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>This paper presents a retrospective analysis of quality management research that has been published in the Quality Management Journal (QMJ) since its inception. The authors use two approaches--a text analysis tool called centering resonance analysis (CRA), supported by a software package called Crawdad, and an analysis of keywords, which has been used in other studies to evaluate bodies of literature. CRA results in word pairings that are influential in predicting the content of articles. The results suggest that the papers published in the journal have adequately addressed the core issues of quality management. To provide additional insight into emerging trends, the authors studied keywords before and after 2002 to analyze changes in research topics during those time periods. This analysis suggests that quality management research has matured and moved beyond the principles of quality and its underlying philosophies, evolving to focus on contemporary issues using better methodologies such as empirical research and case studies. Finally, the authors provide some suggestions for future research in the field.</ab>
        <pubtype>Academic Journal</pubtype>
        <doctype>Article</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="eng">English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=bth&amp;AN=95103086&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="6">
  <header shortDbName="psyh" longDbName="PsycINFO" uiTerm="2010-99240-527">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo>
        <btl>Information systems, competitive dynamics, and firm performance: An interpretive and centering resonance analysis.</btl>
        <aug />
        <isbn>9781109775150</isbn>
      </bkinfo>
      <chapinfo />
      <revinfo />
      <dissinfo>
        <disstl>Information systems, competitive dynamics, and firm performance: An interpretive and centering resonance analysis.</disstl>
      </dissinfo>
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Dissertation Abstracts International: Section B: The Sciences and Engineering</jtl>
        <issn type="Print">04194217</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2010" month="01" day="01">20100101</dt>
        <vid>71</vid>
        <iid>6-B</iid>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ui type="umi">AAI3403777</ui>
        <ppct>1</ppct>
        <pages>3911-3911</pages>
        <tig>
          <atl>Information systems, competitive dynamics, and firm performance: An interpretive and centering resonance analysis.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Vannoy, Sandra A.</au>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="major">Centering</subj>
          <subj type="major">Grounded Theory</subj>
          <subj type="major">Information Systems</subj>
          <subj type="major">Organizational Effectiveness</subj>
          <subj type="major">Vibration</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Internet</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Organizational Behavior</subj>
          <subj type="age">Adulthood (18 yrs &amp; older)</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>This dissertation examines, from a managerial interpretive perspective, how information systems contribute to firms’ specific competitive actions and responses, and the resultant impacts upon firm performance. The findings from this research suggest that the answer may well lie within the role of information systems in firms’ competitive dynamics or the specific competitive actions and/or responses in which firms engage. This dissertation comprises two studies. Study I examines managerial interpretations of the role played by information systems in firms’ competitive dynamics and firm performance. Study II examines the role of social computing and communication technologies in intrafirm social networks and digitally-mediated aggregate cognitive maps at each stage of a competitive dynamics process. The results of Study I in this dissertation suggest a process model, grounded in data from in-depth interviews with executive- and operational-level organizational managers, industry experts and from relevant organizational and industry documents. The relationships inherent in a firm’s information systems, competitive dynamics and firm performance can be traced through four interrelated grounded theoretical categories—IT-enhanced Organizational Information Processing and Competitive Action, Information-driven Competitive Action Decision, Execution/Abandonment, and Firm Performance. Thus, the first study contributes to understanding how information systems enable a process of knowledge dissemination and sharing among managerial decision-makers, how information systems enable a collective and rational competitive action decision-making process, how information systems facilitate and create message channeling systems and create the platform toward competitive actions enactment, and thus, how firm performance is impacted by information systems. This study shows the way in which information systems impact firm performance through the competitive actions and reactions undertaken by a dominant firm. Dominant firms have shown the ability to attain and retain superior performance and exhibit sustained competitive advantage. Thus, the study of the role of information systems in the context of the competitive activity of a dominant firm should be of value to both academics and practitioners. The second study in this dissertation examines the role of social computing and communications technologies in intrafirm social networks and digitally-mediated aggregate cognitive maps embedded within the process of conceiving, enacting and executing firms’ competitive actions and responses and resulting impacts upon firm performance. The role of information systems in this context raises important new issues that have not been addressed by current information systems research. By examining the role of internal managerial social networks formed around social computing and communications technologies that are used in the conception, enactment and execution of firms’ competitive dynamics, it is possible to unearth a more complex and integrated role of information systems in organizations. Study II builds upon the literature in the following areas of research: information systems and firm performance, competitive dynamics in the specific context of the awareness-motivation-capability perspective, social computing, social network theory, and organizational communication in the specific areas of collective and distributed cognition, information seeking and sharing, and organizational memory and learning. The combination of research methods employed in this dissertation makes a unique contribution to research in its own right. The research methodologies used in Study II are Social Network Analysis and Centering Resonance Analysis in conjunction with the Grounded Theoretical findings from Study I. (PsycINFO Database Record (c) 2012 APA, all rights reserved)</ab>
        <pubtype>Dissertation Abstract</pubtype>
        <doctype>Dissertation</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language>English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=psyh&amp;AN=2010-99240-527&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="7">
  <header shortDbName="psyh" longDbName="PsycINFO" uiTerm="2002-12944-001">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo>
        <btl>Studying complex discursive systems: Centering resonance analysis of communication.</btl>
        <aug />
      </bkinfo>
      <chapinfo />
      <revinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Human Communication Research</jtl>
        <issn type="Print">03603989</issn>
        <issn type="Electronic">14682958</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2002" month="04" day="01">20020401</dt>
        <vid>28</vid>
        <iid>2</iid>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ui type="doi">10.1093/hcr/28.2.157</ui>
        <ppct>50</ppct>
        <pages>157-206</pages>
        <tig>
          <atl>Studying complex discursive systems: Centering resonance analysis of communication.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Corman, Steven R.</au>
          <au>Kuhn, Timothy</au>
          <au>McPhee, Robert D.</au>
          <au>Dooley, Kevin J.</au>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="major">Communication Systems</subj>
          <subj type="major">Computer Simulation</subj>
          <subj type="major">Content Analysis</subj>
          <subj type="major">Discourse Analysis</subj>
          <subj type="major">Models</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Centering</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Communications Media</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Vibration</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>Centering resonance analysis (CRA) is a new text analysis method that has broad scope and range and can be applied to large quantities of written text and transcribed conversation. It identifies discursively important words and represents these as a network, then uses structural properties of the network to index word importance. CRA networks can be directly visualized and can be scored for resonance with other networks to support a number of spatial analysis methods. Following a critique of existing methodologies, this paper describes the theoretical basis and operational details of CRA, describes its advantages relative to other techniques, demonstrates its face validity and representational validity, and demonstrates its utility in modeling organizational knowledge. The conclusion argues for its applicability in several organizational research contexts before describing its potential for use in a broader range of applications, including media content analysis, conversation analysis, computer simulations, and models of communication systems. (PsycINFO Database Record (c) 2013 APA, all rights reserved)</ab>
        <pubtype>Journal</pubtype>
        <pubtype>Peer Reviewed Journal</pubtype>
        <doctype>Journal Article</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language>English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=psyh&amp;AN=2002-12944-001&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="8">
  <header shortDbName="a9h" longDbName="Academic Search Complete" uiTerm="102074556">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>International Journal of Mass Spectrometry</jtl>
        <issn>13873806</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2015" month="03" day="15">Mar2015</dt>
        <vid>379</vid>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ui type="doi">10.1016/j.ijms.2014.12.007</ui>
        <ppf>33</ppf>
        <ppct>13</ppct>
        <formats />
        <tig>
          <atl>High-resolution mass separation by phase splitting and fast centering of ion motion in a Penning trap.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Dupré, Pierre</au>
          <au>Lunney, David</au>
          <affil>CSNSM-IN2P3, Université de Paris Sud, Orsay, France</affil>
        </aug>
        <sug />
        <ab>A new technique for fast and effective mass separation of isobaric-contaminant ions is presented based on the continuous control of the phase and magnetron radius of ions orbiting in a Penning trap. Inspired by two techniques: Phase imaging ion cyclotron resonance (PI-ICR) (Eliseev et al., 2013) and magnetron-orbit manipulation (Mortensen et al., 2013), this method does not require ion cooling. First, isobaric species are separated in the radial plane by mass-selective excitations. A radial, position-selective dipole excitation pulse is then applied to re-center only the ions of interest. This paper presents the theoretical analysis of the process with detailed simulations. Results are compared to another buffer-gas free technique: SImultaneous Magnetron and resonant COnversion (SIMCO) excitation (Rosenbusch et al., 2012). Despite a lower maximum resolving power, the new process is twice as fast as SIMCO.</ab>
        <pubtype>Academic Journal</pubtype>
        <doctype>Article</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="eng">English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=a9h&amp;AN=102074556&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="9">
  <header shortDbName="cmedm" longDbName="MEDLINE" uiTerm="23151955">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Human Brain Mapping</jtl>
        <jtl>Hum Brain Mapp</jtl>
        <issn type="Electronic">1097-0193</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2014" month="03" day="01">2014 Mar</dt>
        <vid>35</vid>
        <iid>3</iid>
        <place>United States</place>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ui type="pmid">23151955</ui>
        <ui type="doi">10.1002/hbm.22211</ui>
        <pages>745-59</pages>
        <formats />
        <tig>
          <atl>Logical circularity in voxel-based analysis: normalization strategy may induce statistical bias.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Tustison NJ</au>
          <au>Avants BB</au>
          <au>Cook PA</au>
          <au>Kim J</au>
          <au>Whyte J</au>
          <au>Gee JC</au>
          <au>Stone JR</au>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="major">Brain physiology</subj>
          <subj type="major">Brain Mapping standards</subj>
          <subj type="major">Data Interpretation, Statistical</subj>
          <subj type="major">Magnetic Resonance Imaging standards</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Adult</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Brain physiopathology</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Brain Injuries physiopathology</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Brain Mapping methods</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Female</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Humans</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Magnetic Resonance Imaging methods</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Male</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Middle Aged</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Research Design standards</subj>
          <subj type="age">Adult: 19-44 years</subj>
          <subj type="age">Middle Aged: 45-64 years</subj>
          <subj type="age">All Adult: 19+ years</subj>
          <subj type="gender">Female</subj>
          <subj type="gender">Male</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>Recent discussions within the neuroimaging community have highlighted the problematic presence of selection bias in experimental design. Although initially centering on the selection of voxels during the course of fMRI studies, we demonstrate how this bias can potentially corrupt voxel-based analyses. For such studies, template-based registration plays a critical role in which a representative template serves as the normalized space for group alignment. A standard approach maps each subject's image to a representative template before performing statistical comparisons between different groups. We analytically demonstrate that in these scenarios the popular sum of squared difference (SSD) intensity metric, implicitly surrogating as a quantification of anatomical alignment, instead explicitly maximizes effect size--an experimental design flaw referred to as "circularity bias." We illustrate how this selection bias varies in strength with the similarity metric used during registration under the hypothesis that while SSD-related metrics, such as Demons, will manifest similar effects, other metrics which are not formulated based on absolute intensity differences will produce less of an effect. Consequently, given the variability in voxel-based analysis outcomes with similarity metric choice, we caution researchers specifically in the use of SSD and SSD-related measures where normalization and statistical analysis involve the same image set. Instead, we advocate a more cautious approach where normalization of the individual subject images to the reference space occurs through corresponding image sets which are independent of statistical testing. Alternatively, one can use similarity terms that are less sensitive to this bias.</ab>
        <pubtype>Journal Article</pubtype>
        <doctype>Research Support, U.S. Gov't, Non-P.H.S.</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="eng">English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=cmedm&amp;AN=23151955&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="10">
  <header shortDbName="eric" longDbName="ERIC" uiTerm="EJ659010">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Management Communication Quarterly</jtl>
        <issn type="print">08933189</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2002" month="01" day="01">20020101</dt>
        <vid>16</vid>
        <iid>2</iid>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <pages>274-81</pages>
        <tig>
          <atl>Organizational Knowledge Expression and Management: Centering Resonance Analysis of Organizational Discourse.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>McPhee, Robert D.</au>
          <au>Corman, Steven R.</au>
          <au>Dooley, Kevin</au>
        </aug>
        <su>Discourse Analysis</su>
        <su>Higher Education</su>
        <su>Interpersonal Communication</su>
        <su>Organizational Communication</su>
        <pubtype>Journal Articles</pubtype>
        <pubtype>Opinion Papers</pubtype>
        <doctype>Journal Articles</doctype>
        <doctype>Opinion Papers</doctype>
        <ab>Explores some of the implications of viewing knowledge as crystallized in the verbal expressions of organizational communication. Focuses on one particular approach to knowledge in discourse called centering resonance analysis (CRA). Describes how CRA finds and maps concepts linking diverse chains of discussion and reasoning in and across conversations, then can compare maps between different groups and organizations. (SG)</ab>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="eng">English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=eric&amp;AN=EJ659010&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="11">
  <header shortDbName="bth" longDbName="Business Source Complete" uiTerm="45632584">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Journal of Supply Chain Management</jtl>
        <issn>15232409</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2010" month="01" day="01">Jan2010</dt>
        <vid>46</vid>
        <iid>1</iid>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ui type="doi">10.1111/j.1745-493X.2009.03184.x</ui>
        <ppf>19</ppf>
        <ppct>26</ppct>
        <formats />
        <tig>
          <atl>CORPORATE SOCIAL RESPONSIBILITY REPORTS: A THEMATIC ANALYSIS RELATED TO SUPPLY CHAIN MANAGEMENT.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>TATE, WENDY L.</au>
          <au>ELLRAM, LISA M.</au>
          <au>KIRCHOFF, JON F.</au>
          <affil>University of Tennessee</affil>
          <affil>Miami University</affil>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="thes">SUPPLY chain management</subj>
          <subj type="thes">INDUSTRIAL procurement</subj>
          <subj type="thes">INDUSTRIES -- Environmental aspects</subj>
          <subj type="thes">SOCIOECONOMICS</subj>
          <subj type="unclass">SOCIAL responsibility</subj>
          <subj type="unclass">CRITICAL analysis</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>Firms are increasingly under pressure from stakeholders to incorporate the triple-bottom line of social, environmental and economic responsibility considerations into operations and supply chain management strategies. This research uses content analysis software that performed centering resonance analysis to examine corporate communication to stakeholders through corporate social responsibility (CSR) reports. The intent is to determine how supply chain strategies factor in to the triple-bottom line of 100 socially and environmentally responsible global companies. This research compares and contrasts the influential words in the CSR reports of firms from a range of industries, sizes and geographical regions. The content analysis revealed ten themes that provide a snapshot of how top global companies integrate and improve the triple-bottom line in internal operations and external supply chains. Findings indicated that while institutional pressure is the major driving force behind strategy development for all of the industries studied, companies emphasize different facets of social, environmental and economic responsibility upstream and downstream in supply chains based on industry, size and geographic location. The analysis revealed unique insights regarding corporate communications that other methodologies would not find.</ab>
        <pubtype>Academic Journal</pubtype>
        <doctype>Article</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="eng">English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=bth&amp;AN=45632584&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="12">
  <header shortDbName="a9h" longDbName="Academic Search Complete" uiTerm="96346558">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Food Research International</jtl>
        <issn>09639969</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2014" month="07" day="01">Jul2014</dt>
        <vid>61</vid>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ui type="doi">10.1016/j.foodres.2014.02.048</ui>
        <ppf>75</ppf>
        <ppct>8</ppct>
        <formats />
        <tig>
          <atl>Potential markers of coffee genotypes grown in different Brazilian regions: A metabolomics approach.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>da Silva Taveira, José Henrique</au>
          <au>Borém, Flávio Meira</au>
          <au>Figueiredo, Luísa Pereira</au>
          <au>Reis, Nádia</au>
          <au>Franca, Adriana S.</au>
          <au>Harding, Scott A.</au>
          <au>Tsai, Chung-Jui</au>
          <affil>PPGEA, Universidade Federal de Lavras, Campus Universitário UFLA, S/N, 37200-000 Lavras, MG, Brasil</affil>
          <affil>DEMEC, Universidade Federal de Minas Gerais, Av. Antônio Carlos, 6627, 31270-901 Belo Horizonte, MG, Brasil</affil>
          <affil>Warnell School of Forestry and Natural Resources, Department of Genetics, University of Georgia, Athens, GA, USA</affil>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="thes">BIOCHEMICAL markers in plants</subj>
          <subj type="thes">GENOTYPE-environment interaction</subj>
          <subj type="thes">COFFEE</subj>
          <subj type="thes">PLANT metabolism</subj>
          <subj type="thes">PLANT growth</subj>
          <subj type="naics">Floriculture Production</subj>
          <subj type="unclass">BRAZIL</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>Seeds from different coffee species and coffee from different continents or countries have very distinct chemical composition. However, the differences between genotypes grown at micro-regional levels with similar geographical characteristics are still unclear. In this study, we highlighted the need of using metabolite profiling instead of the usual targeted analysis as a more powerful tool to describe the slight differences between coffees of the same species grown in close origins. Thus, our study focused on finding potential metabolite markers to describe differences of Coffea arabica L. genotypes (Mundo Novo and Bourbons) grown in Brazilian coffee producing municipalities (Lavras, Santo Antônio do Amparo—SAA, and São Sebastião da Grama—SSG). Using the metabolomics approach, 44 metabolites were identified, and some showed great potential for origin and genotype differentiation. The Partial Least Square Discriminant Analysis — PLS-DA model showed that the SAA coffee samples had the most differentiated metabolite profile (approximately 95% accuracy) compared to the other municipalities. The samples from Lavras and SGG had similar profiles (model accuracy of approximately 50%). Potential metabolite markers for the SAA samples included galactinol, fructose, malic acid, oxalic acid, d-glucose, d-sorbitol, galactinol, and myo-inositol. The model used to differentiate the Bourbon and the MN genotype showed 100% accuracy indicating very different metabolite profiles. The features that were most influential in differentiating genotype were: 5-CQA, oxalic acid, galactinol, nicotinic acid, caffeine, and caffeic acid (Bourbon) and myo-inositol, quinic acid, malic acid, fructose, and d-glucose (MN). Enhancing subtle differences in the data by combining information from GC-Q/MS and multivariate analysis resulted in the identification of coffee origins and genotypes as well as the identification of potential markers.</ab>
        <pubtype>Academic Journal</pubtype>
        <doctype>Article</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="eng">English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=a9h&amp;AN=96346558&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="13">
  <header shortDbName="cmedm" longDbName="MEDLINE" uiTerm="21200086">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Zhong Nan Da Xue Xue Bao. Yi Xue Ban = Journal Of Central South University. Medical Sciences</jtl>
        <jtl>Zhong Nan Da Xue Xue Bao Yi Xue Ban</jtl>
        <issn type="Print">1672-7347</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2010" month="12" day="01">2010 Dec</dt>
        <vid>35</vid>
        <iid>12</iid>
        <place>China</place>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ui type="pmid">21200086</ui>
        <ui type="doi">10.3969/j.issn.1672-7347.2010.12.002</ui>
        <pages>1214-8</pages>
        <formats />
        <tig>
          <atl>Metabonomic analysis of rat urine ¹H magnetic resonance spectra based on different normalization methods.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Mamtimin B</au>
          <au>Hasim A</au>
          <au>Chen C</au>
          <au>Upur H</au>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="major">Metabolome</subj>
          <subj type="major">Metabolomics</subj>
          <subj type="major">Nuclear Magnetic Resonance, Biomolecular methods</subj>
          <subj type="major">Urine chemistry</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Animals</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Female</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Male</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Pattern Recognition, Automated</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Rats</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Rats, Wistar</subj>
          <subj type="gender">Female</subj>
          <subj type="gender">Male</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>To study metabonomics in the urine of rats of different genders by magnetic resonance (MR) with 2 normalization methods.</ab>
        <ab>Different normalization methods such as mean-centering not scaling (Ctr) and unit variance scaling (UV) were used before orthogonal to partial least squares discriminant analysis(OPLS-DA). Distinguished metabolites in the urine of different gender rats were analyzed by calculating the correlation coefficients.</ab>
        <ab>The data normalized by Ctr before OPLS-DA analysis revealed high degree conception metabolites in the urine such as valine, alanine, acetate, ornithine, aminohippurate, phenylethylamine, cytosine, citrate, dimethylamine, allantoin, methylamine, fumarate and one unknown metabolite whose chemical shift was δ4.14. Data normalized by UV before OPLS-DA analysis revealed the above 12 high degree conception metabolites except citrate, and also low degree conception metabolites such as thiamine, creatinine, formate and one unknown metabolite whose chemical shift was δ2.92.</ab>
        <ab>Unit variance scaling is a more effective normalization method in metabonomic analysis.</ab>
        <pubtype>Journal Article</pubtype>
        <doctype>Research Support, Non-U.S. Gov't</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="eng">English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=cmedm&amp;AN=21200086&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="14">
  <header shortDbName="a9h" longDbName="Academic Search Complete" uiTerm="44100160">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Chemometrics &amp; Intelligent Laboratory Systems</jtl>
        <issn>01697439</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2009" month="10" day="15">Oct2009</dt>
        <vid>98</vid>
        <iid>2</iid>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ui type="doi">10.1016/j.chemolab.2009.06.004</ui>
        <ppf>173</ppf>
        <ppct>9</ppct>
        <formats />
        <tig>
          <atl>Classification of magnetic resonance images from rabbit renal perfusion.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Gujral, Paman</au>
          <au>Amrhein, Michael</au>
          <au>Bonvin, Dominique</au>
          <au>Vallée, Jean-Paul</au>
          <au>Montet, Xavier</au>
          <au>Michoux, Nicolas</au>
          <affil>Laboratoire d'Automatique, École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne, CH-1015, Lausanne, Switzerland</affil>
          <affil>Digital Imaging Unit, Department of Radiology, University Hospital of Geneva, CH-1211, Geneva, Switzerland</affil>
          <affil>Université Catholique de Louvain, St-Luc University Hospital, Radiodiagnostic Unit, Avenue Hippocrate 10, B-1200 Brussels, Belgium</affil>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="thes">PERFUSION (Physiology)</subj>
          <subj type="thes">CHEMOMETRICS</subj>
          <subj type="thes">KIDNEYS</subj>
          <subj type="thes">MAGNETIC resonance imaging</subj>
          <subj type="thes">RABBITS as laboratory animals</subj>
          <subj type="thes">CONTRAST media (Diagnostic imaging)</subj>
          <subj type="thes">PRINCIPAL components analysis</subj>
          <subj type="thes">LEAST squares</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>Abstract: The feasibility of using chemometric techniques for the automatic detection of whether a rabbit kidney is pathological or not is studied. Sequential images of the kidney are acquired using Dynamic Contrast-Enhanced Magnetic Resonance Imaging with contrast agent injection. A segmentation approach based upon principal component analysis (PCA) is used to separate out the cortex from the rest of the kidney including the medulla, the renal pelvic, and the background. Two classifiers (Soft Independent Method of Class Analogy, SIMCA; Partial Least Squares Discriminant Analysis, PLS-DA) are tested for various types of data pre-treatment including segmentation, feature extraction, centering, autoscaling, standard normal variate transformation, Savitsky-Golay smoothing, and normalization. It is shown that (i) the renal cortex contains more discriminating information on kidney perfusion changes than the whole kidney, and (ii) the PLS-DA classifiers outperform the SIMCA classifiers. PLS-DA, preceded by an automated PCA-based segmentation of kidney anatomical regions, correctly classified all kidneys and constitutes a classification tool of the renal function that can be useful for the clinical diagnosis of renovascular diseases.</ab>
        <pubtype>Academic Journal</pubtype>
        <doctype>Article</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="eng">English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=a9h&amp;AN=44100160&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="15">
  <header shortDbName="cmedm" longDbName="MEDLINE" uiTerm="24721351">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Zhonghua Yi Xue Za Zhi</jtl>
        <jtl>Zhonghua Yi Xue Za Zhi</jtl>
        <issn type="Print">0376-2491</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2014" month="01" day="14">2014 Jan 14</dt>
        <vid>94</vid>
        <iid>2</iid>
        <place>China</place>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ui type="pmid">24721351</ui>
        <pages>115-21</pages>
        <formats />
        <tig>
          <atl>[Meta-analysis of prognostic tests in neonates over 35-week gestational age with hypoxic-ischemic encephalopathy].</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Lin B</au>
          <au>Zhang P</au>
          <au>Cheng G</au>
          <au>Zhou W</au>
          <au>Wang L</au>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="major">Hypoxia-Ischemia, Brain diagnosis</subj>
          <subj type="major">Neonatal Screening methods</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Humans</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Infant, Newborn</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Prognosis</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Sensitivity and Specificity</subj>
          <subj type="age">Infant, Newborn: birth-1 month</subj>
          <subj type="age">All Infant: birth-23 months</subj>
          <subj type="age">All Child: 0-18 years</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>To explore the prognostic value of currently used clinical tests in neonatal patients over 35-week gestational age with perinatal asphyxia and hypoxic-ischemic encephalopathy (HIE).</ab>
        <ab>"Neonate""hypoxic-ischemic encephalopathy " and "prognostic test" were used as key words. Searches were made on the databases of PubMed, EMBASE, CNKI and WanFang for studies published between January 1980 and December 2012. Studies were included if they (1) evaluated outcome in over 35-week gestational age neonates with perinatal asphyxia or HIE; (2) reported outcomes at minimal follow-up age of 18 months; (3) confirmed neurodevelopment with favorable or adverse outcomes. RevMan 5.2 software 1.4 was used for meta-analysis. And the evaluation criteria of each study were employed to assess and analyze the results comprehensively.</ab>
        <ab>Among 260 relevant studies, 20 were included. There are 7 tests contented our inclusion criteria: amplitude-integrated electroencephalography (aEEG), magnetic resonance imaging (MRI:T1/T2 weighted imaging, diffusion weighted imaging (DWI), apparent diffusion coefficient (ADC), magnetic resonance spectroscopy (MR S)), cerebral ultrasound (CUS) and HIE stage. The most promising tests were aEEG: sensitivity 0.936 (95%CI: 0.897-0.964) ; specificity 0.884 (95%CI: 0.836- 0.921). In imaging, T1/T2-weighted MRI sensitivity 0.913 (95%CI: 0.850-0.956), specificity 0.630 (95%CI: 0.544-0.711); diffusion weighted MRI sensitivity 0.933 (95%CI:0.817-0.956), specificity 0.694 (95%CI: 0.546-0.817); ADC sensitivity 0.778 (95%CI: 0.664-0.867) , specificity 0.971 (95%CI: 0.898-0.996); MRS sensitivity 0.918 (95%CI: 0.804-0.977), specificity 0.642 (95%CI: 0.515-0.755). CUS sensitivity 0.683 (95%CI: 0.519-0.819), specificity 0.459 (95%CI: 0.295-0.631). HIE stage sensitivity 0.967 (95%CI: 0.924-0.989) , specificity 0.314 (95%CI: 0.241-0.394).</ab>
        <ab>These evidence suggests an important role for aEEG, MRI (T1/T2-weight, DWI, ADC), CUS and HIE stage. The sensitivity and specificity of aEEG are both relatively high; HIE stage has good sensitivity; in imaging, T1/T2-weight,DWI and MRS yield better sensitivity while ADC has the best specificity. Mild hypothermia treatment reduces the predictive value of evaluation system.Each test has its advantages and disadvantages. Thus an integrated use of a variety of prognostic tests centering on clinical neurological assessment is optimal.</ab>
        <pubtype>Journal Article</pubtype>
        <doctype>English Abstract</doctype>
        <doctype>Meta-Analysis</doctype>
        <doctype>Research Support, Non-U.S. Gov't</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="chi">Chinese</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=cmedm&amp;AN=24721351&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="16">
  <header shortDbName="bth" longDbName="Business Source Complete" uiTerm="93307790">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Business &amp; Society</jtl>
        <issn>00076503</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2014" month="01" day="01">Jan2014</dt>
        <vid>53</vid>
        <iid>1</iid>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ui type="doi">10.1177/0007650311418195</ui>
        <ppf>105</ppf>
        <ppct>29</ppct>
        <formats />
        <tig>
          <atl>Differences Among NGOs in the Business–NGO Cooperative Network.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>O’Connor, Amy</au>
          <au>Shumate, Michelle</au>
          <affil>North Dakota State University, ND, USA</affil>
          <affil>University of Illinois at Urbana–Champaign, IL, USA</affil>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="thes">NONGOVERNMENTAL organizations</subj>
          <subj type="thes">NETWORK analysis (Planning)</subj>
          <subj type="thes">PARTNERSHIP (Business)</subj>
          <subj type="thes">FORTUNE 500 companies</subj>
          <subj type="thes">CORPORATIONS</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>Informed by the symbiotic sustainability model, this theory-building research compares a stratified subsample (N = 66) from 695 nongovernmental organizations (NGOs) that have relationships with U.S. Fortune 500 companies in 11 industries (N = 155). Using network analysis and centering resonance analysis, the research compares the “about us” statements of three groups of NGOs with different indegree centralities. The results of this study suggest that NGOs with multiple corporate partners are distinct from NGOs with single corporate partners. Across all levels of centrality, NGOs in cross-sector cooperative relationships tend to focus on children and be service oriented. In addition, federated NGOs were more likely to occupy a central position in the business–NGO cooperative network and foundations were more likely to have relationships with multiple corporations. Local NGOs were more likely to have only one cross-sector relationship and were, by a significant margin, the largest group. Propositions for future research are offered based on the findings.</ab>
        <pubtype>Academic Journal</pubtype>
        <doctype>Article</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="eng">English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=bth&amp;AN=93307790&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="17">
  <header shortDbName="a9h" longDbName="Academic Search Complete" uiTerm="19934759">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Comptes Rendus Chimie</jtl>
        <issn>16310748</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2006" month="03" day="01">Mar2006</dt>
        <vid>9</vid>
        <iid>3/4</iid>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ui type="doi">10.1016/j.crci.2005.05.012</ui>
        <ppf>498</ppf>
        <ppct>5</ppct>
        <formats />
        <tig>
          <atl>Automatic first-order multiplet analysis in liquid-state NMR.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Prost, Élise</au>
          <au>Bourg, Stéphane</au>
          <au>Nuzillard, Jean-Marc</au>
          <affil>FRE 2715, CPCBAI, Moulin de la Housse, BP 1039, 51687 Reims cedex 2, France</affil>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="thes">NUCLEAR magnetic resonance</subj>
          <subj type="thes">MAGNETIC resonance</subj>
          <subj type="thes">MOLECULES</subj>
          <subj type="thes">SPECTRUM analysis</subj>
          <subj type="thes">BIOMOLECULES</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>Abstract: The extraction of coupling constant values from NMR spectra is an important step in assigning the configuration of organic molecules. A method for the automatic multiplet analysis in weakly coupled spin systems is described here. It relies on a multi-step procedure that forms the AUJ (AUtomatic J) algorithm. Tolerance to low-magnitude second-order effects is achieved by an efficient multiplet centering and symmetrization step. Time-domain signal analysis through a linear model produces a raw evaluation of coupling constants and their associated multiplicities. The final result is obtained through numerical optimization of the multiplet parameters. Two examples are presented, one from an experimental spectrum, and the other one, of higher complexity, from a computer-simulated multiplet. To cite this article: É. Prost et al., C. R. Chimie 9 (2006) .</ab>
        <pubtype>Academic Journal</pubtype>
        <doctype>Article</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="eng">English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=a9h&amp;AN=19934759&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="18">
  <header shortDbName="a9h" longDbName="Academic Search Complete" uiTerm="89032604">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>NeuroImage</jtl>
        <issn>10538119</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2013" month="08" day="01">Aug2013</dt>
        <vid>76</vid>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ui type="doi">10.1016/j.neuroimage.2013.03.004</ui>
        <ppf>183</ppf>
        <ppct>19</ppct>
        <formats />
        <tig>
          <atl>A comprehensive assessment of regional variation in the impact of head micromovements on functional connectomics.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Yan, Chao-Gan</au>
          <au>Cheung, Brian</au>
          <au>Kelly, Clare</au>
          <au>Colcombe, Stan</au>
          <au>Craddock, R. Cameron</au>
          <au>Di Martino, Adriana</au>
          <au>Li, Qingyang</au>
          <au>Zuo, Xi-Nian</au>
          <au>Castellanos, F. Xavier</au>
          <au>Milham, Michael P.</au>
          <affil>Nathan Kline Institute for Psychiatric Research, Orangeburg, NY, USA</affil>
          <affil>Center for the Developing Brain, Child Mind Institute, New York, NY, USA</affil>
          <affil>The Phyllis Green and Randolph Cowen Institute for Pediatric Neuroscience, New York University Child Study Center, New York, NY, USA</affil>
          <affil>Virginia Tech Carilion Research Institute, Roanoke, VA, USA</affil>
          <affil>Key Laboratory of Behavioral Science, Laboratory for Functional Connectome and Development, Magnetic Resonance Imaging Research Center, Institute of Psychology, Chinese Academy of Sciences, Beijing, China</affil>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="thes">NEURAL circuitry</subj>
          <subj type="thes">BRAIN imaging</subj>
          <subj type="thes">BRAIN function localization</subj>
          <subj type="thes">FUNCTIONAL magnetic resonance imaging</subj>
          <subj type="thes">MOTOR ability</subj>
          <subj type="thes">DECISION making</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>Abstract: Functional connectomics is one of the most rapidly expanding areas of neuroimaging research. Yet, concerns remain regarding the use of resting-state fMRI (R-fMRI) to characterize inter-individual variation in the functional connectome. In particular, recent findings that “micro” head movements can introduce artifactual inter-individual and group-related differences in R-fMRI metrics have raised concerns. Here, we first build on prior demonstrations of regional variation in the magnitude of framewise displacements associated with a given head movement, by providing a comprehensive voxel-based examination of the impact of motion on the BOLD signal (i.e., motion–BOLD relationships). Positive motion–BOLD relationships were detected in primary and supplementary motor areas, particularly in low motion datasets. Negative motion–BOLD relationships were most prominent in prefrontal regions, and expanded throughout the brain in high motion datasets (e.g., children). Scrubbing of volumes with FD&gt;0.2 effectively removed negative but not positive correlations; these findings suggest that positive relationships may reflect neural origins of motion while negative relationships are likely to originate from motion artifact. We also examined the ability of motion correction strategies to eliminate artifactual differences related to motion among individuals and between groups for a broad array of voxel-wise R-fMRI metrics. Residual relationships between motion and the examined R-fMRI metrics remained for all correction approaches, underscoring the need to covary motion effects at the group-level. Notably, global signal regression reduced relationships between motion and inter-individual differences in correlation-based R-fMRI metrics; Z-standardization (mean-centering and variance normalization) of subject-level maps for R-fMRI metrics prior to group-level analyses demonstrated similar advantages. Finally, our test–retest (TRT) analyses revealed significant motion effects on TRT reliability for R-fMRI metrics. Generally, motion compromised reliability of R-fMRI metrics, with the exception of those based on frequency characteristics — particularly, amplitude of low frequency fluctuations (ALFF). The implications of our findings for decision-making regarding the assessment and correction of motion are discussed, as are insights into potential differences among volume-based metrics of motion.</ab>
        <pubtype>Academic Journal</pubtype>
        <doctype>Article</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="eng">English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=a9h&amp;AN=89032604&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="19">
  <header shortDbName="a9h" longDbName="Academic Search Complete" uiTerm="25653197">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Journal of the American Chemical Society</jtl>
        <issn>00027863</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2007" month="06" day="27">6/27/2007</dt>
        <vid>129</vid>
        <iid>25</iid>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ppf>7903</ppf>
        <ppct>12</ppct>
        <formats />
        <tig>
          <atl>An Alternating π-Stacked Bisdithiazolyl Radical Conductor.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Leitch, Alicea A.</au>
          <au>Reed, Robert W.</au>
          <au>Robertson, Craig M.</au>
          <au>Britten, James F.</au>
          <au>Xueyang Yu</au>
          <au>Secco, Richard A.</au>
          <au>Oakley, Richard T.</au>
          <affil>Department of Chemistry, University of Waterloo, Waterloo, Ontario N2L 3G1, Canada</affil>
          <affil>Department of Chemistry, McMaster University, Hamilton, Ontario L8S 4L8, Canada</affil>
          <affil>Department of Earth Sciences, University of Western Ontario, London, Ontario N6A 5B7, Canada</affil>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="thes">ELECTRON paramagnetic resonance</subj>
          <subj type="thes">ELECTRON paramagnetic resonance spectroscopy</subj>
          <subj type="thes">ELECTROCHEMICAL analysis</subj>
          <subj type="thes">MAGNETIC susceptibility</subj>
          <subj type="thes">SPECTRUM analysis</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>A general synthetic route to the resonance-stabilized pyrazine-bridged bisdithiazolyl framework, involving the reductive deprotection of 2,6-diaminopyrazine-bisthiocyanate and cyclization with thionyl chloride, has been developed. An N-methyl bisdithiazolyl radical, 4-methyl-4H-bis[1,2,3]dithiazolo[4,5-b: 5′,4′-e]pyrazin-3-yl, has been prepared and characterized solution by electron paramagnetic resonance spectroscopy and cyclic voltammetry. Its crystal structure has been determined at several temperatures. At 295 K, the structure belongs to the space group Cmca and consists of evenly spaced radicals at-stacked in an alternating ABABAB fashion along the x-direction. At 123 K, the space group symmetry is lowered by loss of C-centering to Pccn, so that the radicals are no lodger evenly spaced along the π-stack. At 88 K, a further lowering of space group symmetry to P21/c is observed. Extended Hückel Theory band structure calculations indicate a progressive opening of a band gap at the Fermi level in the low-temperature structures. Magnetic susceptibility measurements over the range 4-300 K reveal essentially diamagnetic behavior below 120 K. Variable-temperature single-crystal conductivity (σ) measurements indicate that the conductivity is activated, even at room temperature, with a room-temperature value σRT = 0.001 S cm-1 and a thermal activation energy Eact = 0.19 eV. Under an applied pressure of 5 GPa, σRT is increased by 3 orders of magnitude, but the conductivity remains activated, with Eact being lowered to 0.11 eV at 5.5 GPa.</ab>
        <pubtype>Academic Journal</pubtype>
        <doctype>Article</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="eng">English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=a9h&amp;AN=25653197&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="20">
  <header shortDbName="f3h" longDbName="Film &amp; Television Literature Index with Full Text" uiTerm="48383711">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>International Communication Gazette</jtl>
        <issn>17480485</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2010" month="03" day="01">Mar2010</dt>
        <vid>72</vid>
        <iid>2</iid>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ppf>151</ppf>
        <ppct>20</ppct>
        <formats />
        <tig>
          <atl>SUCCESS OR CHAOS?</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Garyantes, Dianne M.</au>
          <au>Murphy, Priscilla J.</au>
          <affil>Assistant Professor of Journalism, Rider University, Lawrenceville, NJ</affil>
          <affil>Professor of Communication, Temple University</affil>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="geo">IRAQ</subj>
          <subj type="corp">AL Jazeera (Television network)</subj>
          <subj type="corp">CABLE News Network</subj>
          <subj type="unclass">PRESS &amp; politics</subj>
          <subj type="unclass">TELEVISION broadcasting of news -- Objectivity</subj>
          <subj type="unclass">JOURNALISM -- Objectivity</subj>
          <subj type="unclass">ELECTIONS</subj>
          <subj type="unclass">IDEOLOGY</subj>
          <subj type="unclass">REPRESENTATIVE government</subj>
          <subj type="unclass">NEWS agencies -- Moral &amp; ethical aspects</subj>
          <subj type="unclass">IRAQ -- History -- 2003-</subj>
          <subj type="unclass">IRAQ -- Politics &amp; government -- 2003-</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>This study used computer-assisted textual analysis of frames as ideological cues in news coverage of the Iraqi 2005 elections by CNN.com and Aljazeera.net. CNN's reporting revealed an ideology of a cultural conquest, framing the elections with sentimental patriotism toward western-style democracy. Al Jazeera's texts revealed distrust and suspicion toward the US, framing the elections with skepticism, a lack of legitimacy and chaos. Despite claims of journalistic objectivity, the analysis found a divisive ideology expressed by both news organizations. The study bears out the importance of 'global objectivity' to provide critical, cross-cultural perspectives in an age of expanding media globalization.</ab>
        <pubtype>Academic Journal</pubtype>
        <doctype>Article</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="eng">English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=f3h&amp;AN=48383711&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="21">
  <header shortDbName="cmedm" longDbName="MEDLINE" uiTerm="16118763">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Zeitschrift Für Orthopädie Und Ihre Grenzgebiete</jtl>
        <jtl>Z Orthop Ihre Grenzgeb</jtl>
        <issn type="Print">0044-3220</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2005" month="07" day="01">2005 Jul-Aug</dt>
        <vid>143</vid>
        <iid>4</iid>
        <place>Germany</place>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ui type="pmid">16118763</ui>
        <pages>461-7</pages>
        <formats />
        <tig>
          <atl>[MR-based 3D-analysis of the pathomechanics of traumatic and atraumatic shoulder instability].</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>von Eisenhart-Rothe R</au>
          <au>Hinterwimmer S</au>
          <au>Braune C</au>
          <au>Jäger A</au>
          <au>Mayr H</au>
          <au>Vogl T</au>
          <au>Englmeier KH</au>
          <au>Graichen H</au>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="major">Image Processing, Computer-Assisted</subj>
          <subj type="major">Imaging, Three-Dimensional</subj>
          <subj type="major">Joint Instability physiopathology</subj>
          <subj type="major">Magnetic Resonance Imaging</subj>
          <subj type="major">Shoulder Dislocation physiopathology</subj>
          <subj type="major">Shoulder Joint injuries</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Adolescent</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Adult</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Biomechanical Phenomena</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Female</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Humans</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Joint Instability diagnosis</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Joint Instability surgery</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Male</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Middle Aged</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Postoperative Complications diagnosis</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Postoperative Complications physiopathology</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Range of Motion, Articular physiology</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Recurrence</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Scapula physiopathology</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Shoulder Dislocation diagnosis</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Shoulder Dislocation surgery</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Shoulder Joint physiopathology</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Statistics as Topic</subj>
          <subj type="age">Adolescent: 13-18 years</subj>
          <subj type="age">Adult: 19-44 years</subj>
          <subj type="age">Middle Aged: 45-64 years</subj>
          <subj type="age">All Child: 0-18 years</subj>
          <subj type="age">All Adult: 19+ years</subj>
          <subj type="gender">Female</subj>
          <subj type="gender">Male</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>Until now it is unknown to what extent malpositioning of the scapula is a relevant factor in shoulder instability that should be considered in therapy. The objective was to analyse 3D-scapular kinematics and humeral head (de-)centering in patients with atraumatic and/or traumatic shoulder instability and to investigate the correlation between the two factors.</ab>
        <ab>The shoulders of 28 healthy volunteers and of 14 patients each with atraumatic or traumatic instability were examined in various arm positions - with and without muscle activity - using open MR imaging. After 3D reconstruction, analyses of scapular kinematics and glenohumeral translation were performed.</ab>
        <ab>In atraumatic unstable shoulders, the scapular position [30 degrees of abduction: scapulo-humeral rhythm: 3.5 +/- 2.6 : 1 vs. healthy 2.4 +/- 1.3 : 1; internal rotation: 59 +/- 9 degrees vs. healthy 49 +/- 3 degrees (p &lt; 0.05)] and humeral head position was significantly decentered in both planes (p &lt; 0.05). While the correlation between the two factors was high during passive elevation (r = 0.60-0.87), it was low during muscular activity (r = 0.25-0.62). In patients with traumatic instability no alterations of the scapula kinematics were observed. Significant humeral head decentering (p &lt; 0.05) occurred only during abduction and external rotation.</ab>
        <ab>Patients with atraumatic instability demonstrated significant alterations of scapular kinematics and decentering of the humeral head. In traumatic instability a decentering occurred only in specific arm positions with no changes in scapula position. Because of the high correlation between the two factors, physiotherapeutic strategies for the scapula-stabilising muscles should be adapted to the direction of instability.</ab>
        <pubtype>Journal Article</pubtype>
        <doctype>English Abstract</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="ger">German</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=cmedm&amp;AN=16118763&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="22">
  <header shortDbName="a9h" longDbName="Academic Search Complete" uiTerm="70260523">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Computers in Human Behavior</jtl>
        <issn>07475632</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2012" month="03" day="01">Mar2012</dt>
        <vid>28</vid>
        <iid>2</iid>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ui type="doi">10.1016/j.chb.2011.10.026</ui>
        <ppf>540</ppf>
        <ppct>12</ppct>
        <formats />
        <tig>
          <atl>An approach to measuring influence and cognitive similarity in computer-mediated communication.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Dwyer, Paul</au>
          <affil>Atkinson Graduate School of Management, Willamette University, 900 State Street, Salem, OR 97301, United States</affil>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="thes">CONTENT analysis (Communication)</subj>
          <subj type="thes">BLOGS</subj>
          <subj type="thes">SPECTRUM analysis</subj>
          <subj type="thes">ONLINE chat</subj>
          <subj type="thes">CONVERSATIONAL constraint theory (Communication)</subj>
          <subj type="thes">THEMATIC analysis</subj>
          <subj type="thes">QUALITATIVE research</subj>
          <subj type="thes">COMPUTER networks</subj>
          <subj type="thes">COMMUNICATION</subj>
          <subj type="thes">INTERNET</subj>
          <subj type="thes">INTERPERSONAL relations</subj>
          <subj type="naics">Internet Publishing and Broadcasting and Web Search Portals</subj>
          <subj type="naics">Wired Telecommunications Carriers</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>Abstract: While many explanations of influence have been proposed there is still debate over which is correct even though most are supported by empirical evidence. This uncertainty has been attributed to there being too little evidence of real-world influence networks, and an inability to separate influence from cognitive similarity, that is, a pre-existing like-mindedness, attitude or way of thinking shared among participants. This paper proposes theme resonance, a new metric for measuring both influence and cognitive similarity between and among participants in the same online conversation. Theme resonance is derived from two textual content analysis systems: Centering Resonance Analysis and qualitative thematic modeling. The use of theme resonance is demonstrated by constructing influence networks using online conversations in ten weblogs, allowing the propagation of new conversational themes to be traced from initiator though subsequent propagators. A method of separating influence from like-mindedness is also demonstrated. Depending on the metric chosen influence and its susceptibility were found both to be opposite ends of the same spectrum, and distinct attributes. In either case the majority of blog participants are close to the low end of each characteristic. However, those at the higher ends are shown to be easily and distinctly identified.</ab>
        <pubtype>Academic Journal</pubtype>
        <doctype>Article</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="eng">English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=a9h&amp;AN=70260523&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="23">
  <header shortDbName="a9h" longDbName="Academic Search Complete" uiTerm="89257587">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Materials Letters</jtl>
        <issn>0167577X</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2013" month="05" day="15">May2013</dt>
        <vid>99</vid>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ui type="doi">10.1016/j.matlet.2013.03.043</ui>
        <ppf>180</ppf>
        <ppct>4</ppct>
        <formats />
        <tig>
          <atl>Solution preparation of alloy core–shell nanoparticles: The case of Ni–Cu@Au–Cu nanoparticles.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Chen, Yuanzhi</au>
          <au>Wang, Ziyuan</au>
          <au>Chen, Xiaozhen</au>
          <au>Zeng, Deqian</au>
          <au>Li, Meng</au>
          <au>Peng, Dong-Liang</au>
          <affil>Department of Materials Science and Engineering, College of Materials, Xiamen University, Xiamen 361005, P.R.China</affil>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="thes">SOLUTION (Chemistry)</subj>
          <subj type="thes">NANOPARTICLES</subj>
          <subj type="thes">ALLOYS</subj>
          <subj type="thes">NICKEL compounds</subj>
          <subj type="thes">METALS -- Quenching</subj>
          <subj type="thes">SURFACE plasmon resonance</subj>
          <subj type="naics">All other basic inorganic chemical manufacturing</subj>
          <subj type="naics">Other Basic Inorganic Chemical Manufacturing</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>Abstract: We report a solution method for the preparation of alloy core–shell nanoparticles which consist of Ni–Cu cores and Au–Cu shells. This method involves an injection-quenching step in which Au precursor is injected in and reduced to form alloy shells on pre-formed Ni–Cu cores. The as-prepared Ni–Cu@Au–Cu nanoparticles possess a spherical morphology, and have a typical size of ∼35nm and shell thickness of 6–9nm. The formed core–shell structure has been verified by high-resolution transmission electron microscopy and high-angle annular dark-field imaging along with the analyses of energy-dispersive X-ray spectroscopy. Broadened surface plasmon resonance (SPR) absorption band centering at red light region has been observed. Magnetic measurements reveal room-temperature ferromagnetic properties for the as-prepared Ni–Cu@Au–Cu nanoparticles. The formation of alloy core–shell structure offers tunable optical and magnetic properties for their multiple applications.</ab>
        <pubtype>Academic Journal</pubtype>
        <doctype>Article</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="eng">English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=a9h&amp;AN=89257587&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="24">
  <header shortDbName="cmedm" longDbName="MEDLINE" uiTerm="19317170">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Zhongguo Zhong Xi Yi Jie He Za Zhi Zhongguo Zhongxiyi Jiehe Zazhi = Chinese Journal Of Integrated Traditional And Western Medicine / Zhongguo Zhong Xi Yi Jie He Xue Hui, Zhongguo Zhong Yi Yan Jiu Yuan Zhu Ban</jtl>
        <jtl>Zhongguo Zhong Xi Yi Jie He Za Zhi</jtl>
        <issn type="Print">1003-5370</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2008" month="12" day="01">2008 Dec</dt>
        <vid>28</vid>
        <iid>12</iid>
        <place>China</place>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ui type="pmid">19317170</ui>
        <pages>1112-7</pages>
        <formats />
        <tig>
          <atl>[Metabonomic study on the regulatory effect of xiaoyao powder on chronic immobilization stressed rats].</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Luo HG</au>
          <au>Chen JX</au>
          <au>Yue GX</au>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="major">Drugs, Chinese Herbal administration &amp; dosage</subj>
          <subj type="major">Metabolomics</subj>
          <subj type="major">Stress, Physiological drug effects</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Animals</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Blood Chemical Analysis</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Disease Models, Animal</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Female</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Humans</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Magnetic Resonance Spectroscopy</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Male</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Powders</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Random Allocation</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Rats</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Rats, Sprague-Dawley</subj>
          <subj type="gender">Female</subj>
          <subj type="gender">Male</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>To provide a scientific basis for systematic research on the mechanism of chronic immobilization stress (CIS) induced metabolic network change in rats, through detecting the changes of endogenous metabolites in rats with CIS, treated or un-treated with Xiaoyao Powder (XYP), for determining the small molecule marker compound that closely associated with the metabonomical specificity of CIS and acting mechanism of XYP.</ab>
        <ab>Thirty-six experimental male SD rats were divided into 3 groups, the normal control group, the model group and the XYP group. And all the three groups were subdivided into two subgroups respectively on day 7 and day 21 of the experiment. The stress rat model of CIS was made by chronic restraining method for 3 h every day. Starting from the first day of modeling, XYP 3.854 g/kg in volume of 1 mL/100 g body weight was administered 1 h before restraining via gastrogavage to rats in the XYP group, while equal volume of distilled water was given to rats in the other two groups instead. Blood samples were collected on the 8 th day and 22 th day for detection in the following procedure: at 27 degrees C, 300 microL supernate of blood plasma was taken, calling the Carr-Purcell-Meiboom-Gill (CPMG) and longitudinal eddy-delay (LED) sequence respectively on a Fourier variable nuclear magnetic resonance (NMR) spectrometer, pre-saturated inhibition of the water peak was performed; free induction decay (FID) signals were transferred via 32 k Fourier transformation to gain one-dimensional NMR spectrogram; by taking TSP as the chemical migration reference peak, the segmental integral calculus (0.04 ppm per segment) was performed from 4.5 - 0.5 ppm (CPMG) and 6.0 - 0 ppm (LED) within the peak ranges in 1H spectra using the VNMR software; after normalization, centering and scaling were conducted on data, then used for pattern recognition of principal component analysis (PCA) using the SIMCA-P 10.0 software, or if necessary, the partial least squares discriminate analysis (PLS-DA) was performed.</ab>
        <ab>(1) The metabolites in the model group were significantly different from those in the control group, suggesting that the animal model was successfully established with the metabolic network different to that of control. The model group and the XYP group could be differentiated from the control group by the differences of metabolites and metabolic networks between groups; XYP could intervene the metabolites or the metabolic path to cause changes in final metabolites. (2) The serum contents of lactic acid (1.4, 4.16), choline (3.24), N-acetylgalactosamine (NAC) and saturated fatty acids (1-3) increased, but unsaturated fatty acids (1.99,4-5), blood sugar (34), HDL (0.83), etc. reduced in the CIS rats. XYP showed obvious regulatory effects on final metabolites, causing decrease of lactic acid, choline, NAC, saturated fatty acids and blood sugar, and increase of unsaturated fatty acids, blood sugar, HDL, 3.44 ppm compound, etc.</ab>
        <ab>The metabolic phenotype in CIS rats includes the increase of lactic acid, choline, NAC, saturated fatty acid, and the decrease of blood sugar contents, unsaturated fatty acid, HDL, 3.44 ppm compound, etc., these may be the markers of the metabolites. The final metabolites changes induced by CIS are primarily the lipid substances. XYP markedly regulates the contents of final metabolites, showing the regulatory effects on final metabolites, but what is the metabolite or metabolic pathways it interferes to alter the final metabolites should be confirmed by further studies.</ab>
        <pubtype>Journal Article</pubtype>
        <doctype>English Abstract</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="chi">Chinese</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=cmedm&amp;AN=19317170&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="25">
  <header shortDbName="cmedm" longDbName="MEDLINE" uiTerm="19358232">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Magnetic Resonance In Medicine</jtl>
        <jtl>Magn Reson Med</jtl>
        <issn type="Electronic">1522-2594</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2009" month="06" day="01">2009 Jun</dt>
        <vid>61</vid>
        <iid>6</iid>
        <place>United States</place>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ui type="pmid">19358232</ui>
        <ui type="doi">10.1002/mrm.21873</ui>
        <pages>1441-50</pages>
        <formats />
        <tig>
          <atl>Water saturation shift referencing (WASSR) for chemical exchange saturation transfer (CEST) experiments.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Kim M</au>
          <au>Gillen J</au>
          <au>Landman BA</au>
          <au>Zhou J</au>
          <au>van Zijl PC</au>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="major">Algorithms</subj>
          <subj type="major">Body Water metabolism</subj>
          <subj type="major">Image Interpretation, Computer-Assisted methods</subj>
          <subj type="major">Magnetic Resonance Imaging methods</subj>
          <subj type="major">Muscle, Skeletal anatomy &amp; histology</subj>
          <subj type="major">Muscle, Skeletal metabolism</subj>
          <subj type="major">Water analysis</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Adult</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Female</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Humans</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Image Enhancement methods</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Male</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Reproducibility of Results</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Sensitivity and Specificity</subj>
          <subj type="age">Adult: 19-44 years</subj>
          <subj type="age">All Adult: 19+ years</subj>
          <subj type="gender">Female</subj>
          <subj type="gender">Male</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>Chemical exchange saturation transfer (CEST) is a contrast mechanism that exploits exchange-based magnetization transfer (MT) between solute and water protons. CEST effects compete with direct water saturation and conventional MT processes, and generally can only be quantified through an asymmetry analysis of the water saturation spectrum (Z-spectrum) with respect to the water frequency, a process that is exquisitely sensitive to magnetic field inhomogeneities. Here it is shown that direct water saturation imaging allows measurement of the absolute water frequency in each voxel, allowing proper centering of Z-spectra on a voxel-by-voxel basis independently of spatial B(0) field variations. Optimal acquisition parameters for this "water saturation shift referencing" (WASSR) approach were estimated using Monte Carlo simulations and later confirmed experimentally. The optimal ratio of the WASSR sweep width to the linewidth of the direct saturation curve was found to be 3.3-4.0, requiring a sampling of 16-32 points. The frequency error was smaller than 1 Hz at signal-to-noise ratios of 40 or higher. The WASSR method was applied to study glycogen, where the chemical shift difference between the hydroxyl (OH) protons and bulk water protons at 3T is so small (0.75-1.25 ppm) that the CEST spectrum is inconclusive without proper referencing.</ab>
        <pubtype>Journal Article</pubtype>
        <doctype>Research Support, N.I.H., Extramural</doctype>
        <doctype>Research Support, Non-U.S. Gov't</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="eng">English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=cmedm&amp;AN=19358232&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="26">
  <header shortDbName="cmedm" longDbName="MEDLINE" uiTerm="20373416">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Magnetic Resonance In Medicine</jtl>
        <jtl>Magn Reson Med</jtl>
        <issn type="Electronic">1522-2594</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2010" month="04" day="01">2010 Apr</dt>
        <vid>63</vid>
        <iid>4</iid>
        <place>United States</place>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ui type="pmid">20373416</ui>
        <ui type="doi">10.1002/mrm.22301</ui>
        <pages>1125-34</pages>
        <formats />
        <tig>
          <atl>Echo planar diffusion tensor imaging of the mouse spinal cord at thoracic and lumbar levels: A feasibility study.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Callot V</au>
          <au>Duhamel G</au>
          <au>Le Fur Y</au>
          <au>Decherchi P</au>
          <au>Marqueste T</au>
          <au>Kober F</au>
          <au>Cozzone PJ</au>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="major">Diffusion Magnetic Resonance Imaging methods</subj>
          <subj type="major">Echo-Planar Imaging methods</subj>
          <subj type="major">Spinal Cord anatomy &amp; histology</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Analysis of Variance</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Animals</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Feasibility Studies</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Image Processing, Computer-Assisted</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Lumbar Vertebrae</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Male</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Mice</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Reproducibility of Results</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Sensitivity and Specificity</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Thoracic Vertebrae</subj>
          <subj type="gender">Male</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>Diffusion tensor imaging is increasingly used for probing spinal cord (SC) pathologies, especially in mouse models of human diseases. However, diffusion tensor imaging series requires a long acquisition time and mouse experiments rarely use rapid imaging techniques such as echo planar imaging. A recent preliminary study demonstrated the feasibility and robustness of the echo planar imaging sequence for mouse cervical SC diffusion tensor imaging investigations. The feasibility of echo planar imaging at thoracic and lumbar levels, however, remained unknown due to bulk motion, field inhomogeneities, and off-centering of the SC in the axial plane. In the present study, the feasibility and the robustness of an echo planar imaging-based diffusion tensor imaging sequence for mouse thoracic and lumbar SC investigations is demonstrated. Quantitative and accurate diffusion tensor imaging metrics, as well as high spatially resolved images, have been obtained. This successful demonstration may open new perspectives in the field of mouse SC imaging. Echo planar imaging is used in several imaging modalities, such as relaxometry or perfusion, and may prove to be very attractive for multimodal MR investigations to acquire a more detailed characterization of the SC tissue.</ab>
        <pubtype>Journal Article</pubtype>
        <doctype>Research Support, Non-U.S. Gov't</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="eng">English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=cmedm&amp;AN=20373416&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="27">
  <header shortDbName="cmedm" longDbName="MEDLINE" uiTerm="19526497">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Magnetic Resonance In Medicine</jtl>
        <jtl>Magn Reson Med</jtl>
        <issn type="Electronic">1522-2594</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2009" month="08" day="01">2009 Aug</dt>
        <vid>62</vid>
        <iid>2</iid>
        <place>United States</place>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ui type="pmid">19526497</ui>
        <ui type="doi">10.1002/mrm.21980</ui>
        <pages>384-93</pages>
        <formats />
        <tig>
          <atl>Direct saturation MRI: theory and application to imaging brain iron.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Smith SA</au>
          <au>Bulte JW</au>
          <au>van Zijl PC</au>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="major">Algorithms</subj>
          <subj type="major">Brain anatomy &amp; histology</subj>
          <subj type="major">Brain metabolism</subj>
          <subj type="major">Image Interpretation, Computer-Assisted methods</subj>
          <subj type="major">Iron analysis</subj>
          <subj type="major">Magnetic Resonance Imaging methods</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Adult</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Humans</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Male</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Tissue Distribution</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Young Adult</subj>
          <subj type="age">Adult: 19-44 years</subj>
          <subj type="age">Young Adult: 19-24 years</subj>
          <subj type="age">All Adult: 19+ years</subj>
          <subj type="gender">Male</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>When applying RF saturation to tissue, MRI signal reductions occur due to magnetization transfer (MT) and direct saturation (DS) effects on water protons. It is shown that the direct effects, often considered a nuisance, can be used to distinguish gray matter (GM) regions with different iron content. DS effects were selected by reducing the magnitude and duration of RF irradiation to minimize confounding MT effects. Contrary to MT saturation spectra, direct water saturation spectra are characterized by a symmetric Lorentzian-shaped frequency dependence that can be described by an exact analytical solution of the Bloch equations. The effect of increased transverse relaxation, e.g., due to the presence of iron, will broaden this saturation spectrum. As a first application, DS ratio (DSR) images were acquired to visualize GM structures in the human brain. Similar to T(2)*-weighted images, the quality of DSR images was affected by local field inhomogeneity, but this could be easily corrected for by centering the saturation spectrum on a voxel-by-voxel basis. The results show that, contrary to commonly used T(2)*-weighted and absolute R(2) images, the DSR images visualize all GM structures, including cortex. A direct correlation between DSR and iron content was confirmed for these structures.</ab>
        <pubtype>Journal Article</pubtype>
        <doctype>Research Support, N.I.H., Extramural</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="eng">English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=cmedm&amp;AN=19526497&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="28">
  <header shortDbName="a9h" longDbName="Academic Search Complete" uiTerm="79485642">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>International Journal of Mass Spectrometry</jtl>
        <issn>13873806</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2012" month="07" day="01">Jul2012</dt>
        <vid>325-327</vid>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ui type="doi">10.1016/j.ijms.2012.07.015</ui>
        <ppf>30</ppf>
        <ppct>15</ppct>
        <formats />
        <tig>
          <atl>Theory of simultaneous dipole and quadrupole excitation of the ion motion in a Penning trap.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Kretzschmar, Martin</au>
          <affil>Institut für Physik, Johannes-Gutenberg-Universität, 55099 Mainz, Germany</affil>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="thes">QUADRUPOLES</subj>
          <subj type="thes">PENNING traps</subj>
          <subj type="thes">ION traps</subj>
          <subj type="thes">RADIO frequency</subj>
          <subj type="thes">ULTRAHIGH vacuum</subj>
          <subj type="thes">PHYSICS experiments</subj>
          <subj type="thes">DIPOLE moments</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>Abstract: Penning traps confine ions of atoms and molecules as well as other charged particles by a combination of static electric and magnetic fields to the central region of the trap, where these objects can be studied. Most experiments employ pulses of dipolar radio-frequency radiation followed by pulses of quadrupolar radio-frequency radiation to manipulate the motional state of the trapped particles. Instead of a sequential procedure an excitation of the ion motion by the simultaneous application of dipolar and quadrupolar rf-fields is also conceivable. This paper investigates the theory of simultaneous excitation under very general assumptions, with inclusion of possible damping terms. The equations of motion are formulated and their solution is worked out for the most general case. This work is motivated by recent experiments performed by the ISOLTRAP collaboration aiming at the development of a new technique for the isobaric purification of ion samples that does not make use of buffer gas damping. The ISOLTRAP experiments apply instead simultaneous dipole excitation at the magnetron frequency and resonant interconversion of the radial modes at the cyclotron frequency (SIMCO excitation). Such a technique will be of great importance for experiments with highly charged ions because it can be utilized in ultrahigh vacuum and thus avoids unwanted charge exchange effects due to collisions with neutral atoms. This paper presents a detailed theoretical analysis of the new method.</ab>
        <pubtype>Academic Journal</pubtype>
        <doctype>Article</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="eng">English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=a9h&amp;AN=79485642&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="29">
  <header shortDbName="psyh" longDbName="PsycINFO" uiTerm="2014-25684-001">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo>
        <btl>Have global ethical values emerged in the public relations industry? Evidence from national and international professional public relations associations.</btl>
        <aug />
      </bkinfo>
      <chapinfo />
      <revinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Journal of Business Ethics</jtl>
        <issn type="Print">01674544</issn>
        <issn type="Electronic">15730697</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2014" month="06" day="19">20140619</dt>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ui type="doi">10.1007/s10551-014-2226-4</ui>
        <tig>
          <atl>Have global ethical values emerged in the public relations industry? Evidence from national and international professional public relations associations.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Taylor, Maureen</au>
          <au>Yang, Aimei</au>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="unclass">No terms assigned</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>Globalization has the potential to create a network society where “there is a common cultural code of values that forms the glue of the network” (Castells, The rise of the network society: The information age: economy, society, and culture, 2000). This article explores if common cultural codes of values are emerging in the public relations industry by examining the codes of ethics of 41 professional public relations associations across the world. The method for the analysis was Centering Resonance Analysis, a textual analysis methodology, that uses linguistics theory to assess main concepts, their influence, and their interrelationships (Canary and Jennings, J Bus Ethics 80: 263–278, 2008; Corman et al., Hum Commun Res 28: 157–206, 2002). The research team found that six dominant themes emerged from the codes of ethics of professional communication associations: (1) professionalism, (2) advocacy, (3) moral standards, (4) clients’ interests, (5) expertise, and (6) relationships. The findings suggest that global values that will influence organizational relationships with publics are emerging in professional communication practice. (PsycINFO Database Record (c) 2014 APA, all rights reserved)</ab>
        <pubtype>Journal</pubtype>
        <pubtype>Peer Reviewed Journal</pubtype>
      </artinfo>
      <language>English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=psyh&amp;AN=2014-25684-001&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="30">
  <header shortDbName="cmedm" longDbName="MEDLINE" uiTerm="2362201">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Journal Of Nuclear Medicine: Official Publication, Society Of Nuclear Medicine</jtl>
        <jtl>J Nucl Med</jtl>
        <issn type="Print">0161-5505</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="1990" month="07" day="01">1990 Jul</dt>
        <vid>31</vid>
        <iid>7</iid>
        <place>UNITED STATES</place>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ui type="pmid">2362201</ui>
        <pages>1220-6</pages>
        <formats />
        <tig>
          <atl>Correlation methods for the centering, rotation, and alignment of functional brain images.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Junck L</au>
          <au>Moen JG</au>
          <au>Hutchins GD</au>
          <au>Brown MB</au>
          <au>Kuhl DE</au>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="major">Brain radionuclide imaging</subj>
          <subj type="major">Image Processing, Computer-Assisted methods</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Aged</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Brain metabolism</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Glucose metabolism</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Humans</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Magnetic Resonance Imaging</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Rotation</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Tomography, Emission-Computed</subj>
          <subj type="age">Aged: 65+ years</subj>
          <subj type="age">All Adult: 19+ years</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>Simple methods are described using correlation analysis to rotate functional brain images to a standard vertical orientation, identify the antero-posterior centerline, and align multiple images from the same brain level. Image rotation and centering are performed by determining the angle of rotation and centerline coordinate that result in maximal left-right correlation. Testing of this method on sets of multiple images acquired simultaneously through different brain levels suggests that the optimal rotation can be determined within 1 degree and the centerline within 0.3 mm. Spatial alignment of two or more images from the same brain level of a single subject is accomplished by finding the translation and rotation that yield the highest correlation between the images. Testing of the alignment method on sets of simultaneously acquired images at multiple brain levels suggests that the optimal translation can be determined within 0.45-0.69 mm and the optimal rotation within 0.8 degrees. These methods are completely objective and can easily be automated.</ab>
        <pubtype>Journal Article</pubtype>
        <doctype>Research Support, Non-U.S. Gov't</doctype>
        <doctype>Research Support, U.S. Gov't, P.H.S.</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="eng">English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=cmedm&amp;AN=2362201&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="31">
  <header shortDbName="a9h" longDbName="Academic Search Complete" uiTerm="11098642">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Journal of Magnetic Resonance</jtl>
        <issn>10907807</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2003" month="11" day="01">Nov2003</dt>
        <vid>165</vid>
        <iid>1</iid>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ui type="doi">10.1016/S1090-7807(03)00275-1</ui>
        <ppf>137</ppf>
        <ppct>16</ppct>
        <formats />
        <tig>
          <atl>Aqueous flat cells perpendicular to the electric field for use in electron paramagnetic resonance spectroscopy.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Mett, Richard R.</au>
          <au>Hyde, James S.</au>
          <affil>Department of Biophysics, Medical College of Wisconsin, Milwaukee, WI 53226-0509, USA</affil>
          <affil>Milwaukee School of Engineering, Milwaukee, WI 53202-3109, USA</affil>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="thes">MAXWELL equations</subj>
          <subj type="thes">ELECTRON paramagnetic resonance</subj>
          <subj type="thes">ELECTRIC fields</subj>
          <subj type="thes">ELECTRON paramagnetic resonance spectroscopy</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>An analytic solution of the Maxwell equations for aqueous flat cells in rectangular TE102 cavities has led to the prediction of significant (3–6 times) X-band EPR signal improvement over the standard flat cell for a new sample configuration consisting of many flat cells oriented perpendicular to the electric field nodal plane. Analytic full wave solutions in the presence of sample and wall losses have been obtained and numerically evaluated. Observation of the predicted fields led to a classification of three distinct types of sample loss mechanisms, which, in turn inspired sample designs that minimize each loss type. The resulting EPR signal enhancement is due to the presence and centering of a tangential electric field node within each individual sample region. Samples that saturate with the available RF magnetic field and those that do not are considered. Signal enhancement appears in both types. These observations, done for the TE102 mode, carry over to the uniform field (UF) modes, a relatively new class of microwave cavities for use in EPR spectroscopy developed in this laboratory. Rectangular UF modes have an RF magnetic field magnitude that is uniform in a plane. Based on this analysis, a practical multiple flat-cell design is proposed.</ab>
        <pubtype>Academic Journal</pubtype>
        <doctype>Article</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="eng">English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=a9h&amp;AN=11098642&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="32">
  <header shortDbName="bth" longDbName="Business Source Complete" uiTerm="12202930">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>IEEE Transactions on Advanced Packaging</jtl>
        <issn>15213323</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2003" month="11" day="01">Nov2003</dt>
        <vid>26</vid>
        <iid>4</iid>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ui type="doi">10.1109/TADVP.2003.821081</ui>
        <ppf>375</ppf>
        <ppct>10</ppct>
        <formats />
        <tig>
          <atl>Coupling of Vias in Electronic Packaging and Printed Circuit Board Structures With Finite Ground Plane.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Leung Tsang</au>
          <au>Miller, Dennis</au>
          <affil>Department of Electronic Engineering, City University of Hong Kong, Hong Kong.</affil>
          <affil>Department of Electrical Engineering, University of Washington, Seattle, WA 98195 USA.</affil>
          <affil>Jones Farm Campus, INTEL Corporation, Hillsboro, OR 97124 USA.</affil>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="thes">ELECTRONIC packaging</subj>
          <subj type="thes">MICROELECTRONICS</subj>
          <subj type="naics">Electronic components, navigational and communications equipment and supplies merchant wholesalers</subj>
          <subj type="naics">Printed Circuit Assembly (Electronic Assembly) Manufacturing</subj>
          <subj type="naics">Bare Printed Circuit Board Manufacturing</subj>
          <subj type="naics">Semiconductor and other electronic component manufacturing</subj>
          <subj type="naics">Other Electronic Parts and Equipment Merchant Wholesalers</subj>
          <subj type="unclass">RESONANCE</subj>
          <subj type="unclass">PRINTED circuits</subj>
          <subj type="unclass">SIGNAL processing</subj>
          <subj type="unclass">ELECTRIC circuits</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>A full wave method is presented for modeling and analyzing multiple interactions among vertical vias in densely packaged integrated circuits and printed circuit board with ground plane of finite extent. In such structures, the TEM mode in the planar structure is excited and can propagate and cause interaction of waves among vias. Reflections will also occur at the edges of the finite ground plane. The electromagnetic analysis methodology is an extension of the previous methodology in analyzing multiple scattering among vias for infinite ground plane [1]-[3]. The analysis is based upon the cylindrical wave mode expansion of the magnetic field Green's function, the Foldy-Lax multiple scattering formalism and utilizing the resonator modes of a circular cavity. The circular resonator modes are transformed into cylindrical waves onto the cylindrical via structures. Numerical results illustrate the physics of the underlying resonance scattering problems. We consider the cases of a) two coupled active vias of differential mode and b) two coupled vias of common mode. Results are also illustrated for ground plane resonance and the effects of shorting vias on such resonance. The effects of off-centering and the presence of idle vias are also illustrated.</ab>
        <pubtype>Academic Journal</pubtype>
        <doctype>Article</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="eng">English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=bth&amp;AN=12202930&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="33">
  <header shortDbName="bth" longDbName="Business Source Complete" uiTerm="44081431">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Journal of Public Relations Research</jtl>
        <issn>1062726X</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2009" month="10" day="01">Oct2009</dt>
        <vid>21</vid>
        <iid>4</iid>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ui type="doi">10.1080/10627260902966425</ui>
        <ppf>361</ppf>
        <ppct>20</ppct>
        <formats>
          <fmt type="PDF" size="354KB" />
        </formats>
        <tig>
          <atl>The Leader as the Face of a Crisis: Philip Morris' CEO's Speeches During the 1990s.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Oliveira, Maria de Fatima</au>
          <au>Murphy, Priscilla</au>
          <affil>Mass Media and Communication Doctoral Program, Temple University</affil>
          <affil>Department of Strategic &amp; Organizational Communication, Temple University</affil>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="thes">RESEARCH</subj>
          <subj type="thes">LEADERSHIP</subj>
          <subj type="thes">CORPORATE image</subj>
          <subj type="thes">CHIEF executive officers</subj>
          <subj type="geo">RICHMOND (Va.)</subj>
          <subj type="geo">VIRGINIA</subj>
          <subj type="corp">PHILIP Morris Operations Center (Richmond, Va.)</subj>
          <subj type="unclass">SPEECH</subj>
          <subj type="unclass">CRISIS communication</subj>
          <subj type="unclass">LEGAL status, laws, etc.</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>This research investigated Philip Morris' crisis communication management strategies during the 1990s through the study of its CEO's speeches. This analysis explored the company's maneuvers to camouflage controversies in acceptable social expectations. Pairing framing theory with centering resonance analysis, this research found 3 distinct frames: profitable multinational (1994-1996), litigation target (1997-1998), and corporate good citizen (1999-2001). Avoidance of talk about health issues indicated the company's strategic adaptation to a shifting legal and public opinion climate, as it sought to authenticate its right to do business by reframing the notion of corporate responsibility away from healthy products and toward high-price philanthropy.</ab>
        <pubtype>Academic Journal</pubtype>
        <doctype>Article</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="eng">English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=bth&amp;AN=44081431&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="34">
  <header shortDbName="psyh" longDbName="PsycINFO" uiTerm="2009-99100-387">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo>
        <btl>Facilitators' perceptions of what contributes to group synergy and collective resonance.</btl>
        <aug />
        <isbn>9780549892403</isbn>
      </bkinfo>
      <chapinfo />
      <revinfo />
      <dissinfo>
        <disstl>Facilitators' perceptions of what contributes to group synergy and collective resonance.</disstl>
      </dissinfo>
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Dissertation Abstracts International: Section B: The Sciences and Engineering</jtl>
        <issn type="Print">04194217</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2009" month="01" day="01">20090101</dt>
        <vid>69</vid>
        <iid>11-B</iid>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ui type="umi">AAI3331299</ui>
        <ppct>1</ppct>
        <pages>7194-7194</pages>
        <tig>
          <atl>Facilitators' perceptions of what contributes to group synergy and collective resonance.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Wilson, Allison Cressy</au>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="major">Empowerment</subj>
          <subj type="major">Professional Development</subj>
          <subj type="major">Vibration</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Environment</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Qualitative Research</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>The purpose of this study was to discover what factors facilitators believe contribute to synergy or collective resonance in groups. The research questions included: (1) How do facilitators describe experiences of collective resonance? (2) What do facilitators believe are key factors that foster environments of collective resonance? (3) How do they believe their role as a facilitator contributes to experiences of collective resonance? Research interviewing was used for data collection in this qualitative study and thematic analysis was used for data analysis. Thirty group facilitators from a broad range of settings were interviewed by phone about experiences of group synergy and collective resonance in groups. Key features of collective resonance included: positive group dynamics, a sense of timelessness, and a felt sense of energy, emotion, and vibration. In addition, there are factors that helped groups shift into resonance such as shared stories and dialogue, having a sacred space or container, and using multi-sensory approaches. Facilitator qualities that contribute to resonance included: effective facilitation skills, facilitator centeredness, effective pre-assessment, and creating a safe container for group work. Facilitators noted that resonance benefits facilitators and groups. Facilitator benefits included personal empowerment, affirmation and enhancement of their work, and an increased sense of connection with groups. Groups benefited by having, improved group process, personal growth and development, an increased sense of interconnection and expanded capabilities in future group experiences. The findings of this study underscore the importance of the inner world of facilitation that includes how facilitators prepare for work with groups internally and how they use intuition and sensing to guide their practice in the midst of group experiences. This study could stimulate further inquiry about intrapersonal dimensions of facilitators including spiritual and centering practices, intuition and sensing, and how facilitators attune to the subtler, energetic aspects of facilitation in order to become more reflective and effective group facilitators. Suggestions for future research emphasized utilizing the findings of this study to enhance the preparation and professional development of group facilitators to maximize the benefits of collective resonance and improve group outcomes. (PsycINFO Database Record (c) 2012 APA, all rights reserved)</ab>
        <pubtype>Dissertation Abstract</pubtype>
        <doctype>Dissertation</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language>English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=psyh&amp;AN=2009-99100-387&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="35">
  <header shortDbName="cmedm" longDbName="MEDLINE" uiTerm="20014064">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Movement Disorders: Official Journal Of The Movement Disorder Society</jtl>
        <jtl>Mov Disord</jtl>
        <issn type="Electronic">1531-8257</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2010" month="04" day="15">2010 Apr 15</dt>
        <vid>25</vid>
        <iid>5</iid>
        <place>United States</place>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ui type="pmid">20014064</ui>
        <ui type="doi">10.1002/mds.22913</ui>
        <pages>552-9</pages>
        <formats />
        <tig>
          <atl>Myopathy causing camptocormia in idiopathic Parkinson's disease: a multidisciplinary approach.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Spuler S</au>
          <au>Krug H</au>
          <au>Klein C</au>
          <au>Medialdea IC</au>
          <au>Jakob W</au>
          <au>Ebersbach G</au>
          <au>Gruber D</au>
          <au>Hoffmann KT</au>
          <au>Trottenberg T</au>
          <au>Kupsch A</au>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="major">Muscular Diseases complications</subj>
          <subj type="major">Parkinson Disease complications</subj>
          <subj type="major">Spinal Curvatures etiology</subj>
          <subj type="major">Ubiquitin-Protein Ligases genetics</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Aged</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Case-Control Studies</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Desmin metabolism</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Dystrophin metabolism</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Electromyography methods</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Electron Transport Complex IV metabolism</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Female</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Head pathology</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Humans</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Magnetic Resonance Imaging methods</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Male</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Middle Aged</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Muscle, Skeletal metabolism</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Muscle, Skeletal physiopathology</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Muscular Diseases genetics</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Muscular Diseases pathology</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Neck Muscles metabolism</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Neck Muscles physiopathology</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Parkinson Disease genetics</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Parkinson Disease pathology</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Point Mutation</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Retrospective Studies</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Spinal Curvatures genetics</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Spinal Curvatures pathology</subj>
          <subj type="age">Aged: 65+ years</subj>
          <subj type="age">Middle Aged: 45-64 years</subj>
          <subj type="age">All Adult: 19+ years</subj>
          <subj type="gender">Female</subj>
          <subj type="gender">Male</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>Extreme forward flexion of the spine, named camptocormia (CC), and head drop syndrome (HD) may be among the most disabling symptoms in Parkinson's disease (PD). This study aims to eludicate the etiology of PD-associated CC and HD via a multidisciplinary approach (clinical examination, electromyography, MRI, genetic analysis, muscle morphology) centering on the histology of the paraspinal muscles. We studied 17 patients with the clinical diagnosis of PD and CC or head drop syndrome and six controls. We performed muscle biopsies of paraspinal muscles and deep neck extensor muscles. Mean age at onset of postural abnormality was 66 years and mean latency between onset of parkinsonian symptoms to first signs of CC or head drop was 7 years. The electromyogram of paraspinal muscles was abnormal in 13-14 patients. Histopathology revealed chronic myopathic changes in 14 of 17 biopsies, consisting of abnormal variation in fiber size, increase in internal nuclei, and increase in connective tissue, myofibrillar disarray and similarities to protein surplus myopathies. Interestingly, heterozygous variants in the Parkin gene were found in 2 of 9 investigated patients. We conclude that CC and HD in PD are predominantly myopathic. Aberrant protein aggregation may link PD and CC.</ab>
        <pubtype>Journal Article</pubtype>
        <doctype>Research Support, Non-U.S. Gov't</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="eng">English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=cmedm&amp;AN=20014064&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="36">
  <header shortDbName="psyh" longDbName="PsycINFO" uiTerm="2010-25000-001">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo>
        <btl>The saccadic re-centering bias is associated with activity changes in the human superior colliculus.</btl>
        <aug />
      </bkinfo>
      <chapinfo />
      <revinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Frontiers in Human Neuroscience</jtl>
        <issn type="Electronic">16625161</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2010" month="11" day="01">20101101</dt>
        <vid>4</vid>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ui type="doi">10.3389/fnhum.2010.00193</ui>
        <ui type="pmid">21103010</ui>
        <tig>
          <atl>The saccadic re-centering bias is associated with activity changes in the human superior colliculus.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Krebs, Ruth M.</au>
          <au>Schoenfeld, Mircea A.</au>
          <au>Boehler, Carsten N.</au>
          <au>Song, Allen W.</au>
          <au>Woldorff, Marty G.</au>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="major">Neurons</subj>
          <subj type="major">Superior Colliculus</subj>
          <subj type="major">Functional Magnetic Resonance Imaging</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Centering</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Eye Movements</subj>
          <subj type="age">Adulthood (18 yrs &amp; older)</subj>
          <subj type="gender">Male</subj>
          <subj type="gender">Female</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>Being able to effectively explore our visual world is of fundamental importance, and it has been suggested that the straight-ahead gaze (primary position) might play a special role in this context. We employed fMRI in humans to investigate how neural activity might be modulated for saccades relative to this putative default position. Using an endogenous cueing paradigm, saccade direction and orbital starting position were systematically manipulated, resulting in saccades toward primary position (centripetal) and away from primary position (centrifugal) that were matched in amplitude, directional predictability, as well as orbital starting position. In accord with earlier research, we found that fMRI activity in the superior colliculus (SC), as well as in the frontal eye fields and the intraparietal sulcus, was enhanced contralateral to saccade direction across all saccade conditions. Furthermore, the SC exhibited a relative activity decrease during re-centering relative to centrifugal saccades, a pattern that was paralleled by faster saccadic reaction times. In contrast, activity within the cortical eye fields was not significantly modulated during re-centering saccades as compared to other saccade types, suggesting that the re-centering bias is predominantly implemented at a subcortical rather than cortical processing stage. Such a modulation might reflect a special coding bias facilitating the return of gaze to a default position in the gaze space in which retinotopic and egocentric reference frames are aligned and from which the visual world can be effectively explored. (PsycINFO Database Record (c) 2012 APA, all rights reserved)</ab>
        <pubtype>Journal</pubtype>
        <pubtype>Peer Reviewed Journal</pubtype>
        <doctype>Journal Article</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language>English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=psyh&amp;AN=2010-25000-001&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="37">
  <header shortDbName="a9h" longDbName="Academic Search Complete" uiTerm="42095105">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Source Code for Biology &amp; Medicine</jtl>
        <issn>17510473</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2009" month="01" day="01">2009</dt>
        <vid>4</vid>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ui type="doi">10.1186/1751-0473-4-3</ui>
        <ppf>1</ppf>
        <ppct>14</ppct>
        <formats>
          <fmt type="PDF" size="1.8MB" />
        </formats>
        <tig>
          <atl>KinImmerse: Macromolecular VR for NMR ensembles.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Block, Jeremy N.</au>
          <au>Zielinski, David J.</au>
          <au>Chen, Vincent B.</au>
          <au>Davis, Ian W.</au>
          <au>Vinson, E. Claire</au>
          <au>Brady, Rachael</au>
          <au>Richardson, Jane S.</au>
          <au>Richardson, David C.</au>
          <affil>Biochemistry Department, Duke University Medical Center, Durham, NC 27710, USA</affil>
          <affil>Visualization Technology Group, Pratt School of Engineering, Duke University, Durham, NC 27706, USA</affil>
          <affil>Electrical and Computer Engineering Department, Pratt School of Engineering, Duke University, Durham, NC 27706, USA</affil>
          <affil>Biochemistry Department, University of Washington, Seattle, WA 98195, USA</affil>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="thes">VIRTUAL reality</subj>
          <subj type="thes">MANIPULATIVE behavior</subj>
          <subj type="thes">VISUALIZATION</subj>
          <subj type="thes">COMMUNITY relations</subj>
          <subj type="thes">COMPUTER simulation</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>Background: In molecular applications, virtual reality (VR) and immersive virtual environments have generally been used and valued for the visual and interactive experience - to enhance intuition and communicate excitement - rather than as part of the actual research process. In contrast, this work develops a software infrastructure for research use and illustrates such use on a specific case. Methods: The Syzygy open-source toolkit for VR software was used to write the KinImmerse program, which translates the molecular capabilities of the kinemage graphics format into software for display and manipulation in the DiVE (Duke immersive Virtual Environment) or other VR system. KinImmerse is supported by the flexible display construction and editing features in the KiNG kinemage viewer and it implements new forms of user interaction in the DiVE. Results: In addition to molecular visualizations and navigation, KinImmerse provides a set of research tools for manipulation, identification, co-centering of multiple models, free-form 3D annotation, and output of results. The molecular research test case analyzes the local neighborhood around an individual atom within an ensemble of nuclear magnetic resonance (NMR) models, enabling immersive visual comparison of the local conformation with the local NMR experimental data, including target curves for residual dipolar couplings (RDCs). Conclusion: The promise of KinImmerse for production-level molecular research in the DiVE is shown by the locally co-centered RDC visualization developed there, which gave new insights now being pursued in wider data analysis.</ab>
        <pubtype>Academic Journal</pubtype>
        <doctype>Article</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="eng">English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=a9h&amp;AN=42095105&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="38">
  <header shortDbName="bth" longDbName="Business Source Complete" uiTerm="95103084">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Quality Management Journal</jtl>
        <issn>10686967</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2013" month="01" day="01">2013</dt>
        <vid>20</vid>
        <iid>1</iid>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ppf>5</ppf>
        <ppct>2</ppct>
        <formats>
          <fmt type="PDF" size="77KB" />
        </formats>
        <tig>
          <atl>Executive Briefs.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug />
        <sug>
          <subj type="thes">TOTAL quality management</subj>
          <subj type="thes">MANAGEMENT research</subj>
          <subj type="thes">INDUSTRIAL management</subj>
          <subj type="thes">MANAGEMENT science</subj>
          <subj type="thes">BEST practices</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>This section offers quality management research news briefs as of January 2013. One study utilized analytical techniques in reviewing themes and emerging trends in quality management research. Another research examined previous quality management studies with the use of centering resonance analysis and keyword analysis. An outlook for the quality management discipline particularly in terms of implementation and standards is also presented.</ab>
        <pubtype>Academic Journal</pubtype>
        <doctype>Article</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="eng">English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=bth&amp;AN=95103084&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="39">
  <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="311114">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo>
        <btl>Earthquake Engineering : New Research</btl>
        <aug>
          <au>Ikeda, Yuuki</au>
          <au>Miura, Takumi</au>
        </aug>
        <isbn type="print">9781604567366</isbn>
        <isbn type="electronic">9781608765560</isbn>
      </bkinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2009" month="01" day="01"></dt>
        <place>New York</place>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <formats>
          <fmt type="" />
        </formats>
        <tig>
          <atl>Earthquake Engineering : New Research</atl>
        </tig>
        <sug>
          <subj type="bisac">TECHNOLOGY &amp; ENGINEERING / Civil / Earthquake</subj>
          <subj type="unclass">Earthquake engineering</subj>
        </sug>
        <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
        <doctype>Book</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="eng">English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=311114&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="40">
  <header shortDbName="a9h" longDbName="Academic Search Complete" uiTerm="13834024">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Journal of Engineering Mechanics</jtl>
        <issn>07339399</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2004" month="08" day="01">Aug2004</dt>
        <vid>130</vid>
        <iid>8</iid>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ui type="doi">10.1061/(ASCE)0733-9399(2004)130:8(894)</ui>
        <ppf>894</ppf>
        <ppct>10</ppct>
        <formats>
          <fmt type="PDF" size="172KB" />
        </formats>
        <tig>
          <atl>Frequency Response of Flag-Shaped Single Degree-of-Freedom Hysteretic Systems.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Christopoulos, Constantin</au>
          <affil>Assistant Professor, Dept. of Civil Engineering, Univ. of Toronto, 35 St.-George St., Toronto ON, Canada M5S 1A4</affil>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="thes">FREQUENCY response (Dynamics)</subj>
          <subj type="thes">ENERGY dissipation</subj>
          <subj type="thes">RESIDUAL stresses</subj>
          <subj type="thes">DEFORMATIONS (Mechanics)</subj>
          <subj type="thes">HYSTERESIS</subj>
          <subj type="thes">ELASTOPLASTICITY</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>Recognizing the importance of limiting residual deformations that are usually associated with the response of full hysteretic systems under seismic loading, a number of energy dissipating devices and innovative structural systems exhibiting a full recentering response have recently been developed. Although these systems encompass the highly desirable self-centering characteristic, they inherently have less energy dissipation capacity when compared to more traditional fuller hysteretic systems. Little information is available on the nonlinear dynamics of systems exhibiting this flag-shaped hysteresis. In this paper, the frequency response of single degree of freedom (SDOF) systems exhibiting the flag-shaped hysteresis is computed in a closed form using the method of slowly varying parameters. The solution is derived for two independent variables representing the postyielding stiffness and energy dissipation capacity that define all self-centering hysteretic systems. The hysteretic systems covered by this formulation range from bilinear elastic systems (with no energy dissipation) to full bilinear elastoplastic. The frequency response exhibits a softening branch with multiple solution regions. A relationship between the system properties and bounded response at resonance for a given amplitude of excitation is also derived. Further analysis is carried out to assess the stability of these multiple solution regions. It is found that both stable solution branches can be achieved depending on the nature of the excitation. An amplitude jump phenomenon is also present both in increasing frequency and decreasing frequency sweeps. The concept of theoretical versus likely response curve is discussed for less idealized excitation functions.</ab>
        <pubtype>Academic Journal</pubtype>
        <doctype>Article</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="eng">English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=a9h&amp;AN=13834024&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="41">
  <header shortDbName="nlebk" longDbName="eBook Collection (EBSCOhost)" uiTerm="203085">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo>
        <btl>Superconductivity</btl>
        <aug>
          <au>Poole, Charles P.</au>
        </aug>
        <isbn type="print">9780120887613</isbn>
        <isbn type="electronic">9780080550480</isbn>
      </bkinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2007" month="01" day="01"></dt>
        <ed>2nd ed</ed>
        <place>Amsterdam</place>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <formats>
          <fmt type="" />
        </formats>
        <tig>
          <atl>Superconductivity</atl>
        </tig>
        <sug>
          <subj type="bisac">SCIENCE / Physics / General</subj>
          <subj type="unclass">Superconductivity</subj>
        </sug>
        <pubtype>eBook</pubtype>
        <doctype>Book</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="eng">English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=nlebk&amp;AN=203085&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="42">
  <header shortDbName="psyh" longDbName="PsycINFO" uiTerm="2012-35075-008">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo>
        <btl>An imprisoning gaze: Practices of gendered, racialized and epistemic violence.</btl>
        <aug />
      </bkinfo>
      <chapinfo />
      <revinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>International Review of Victimology</jtl>
        <issn type="Print">02697580</issn>
        <issn type="Electronic">20479433</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2013" month="01" day="01">20130101</dt>
        <vid>19</vid>
        <iid>1</iid>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ui type="doi">10.1177/0269758012447219</ui>
        <ppct>12</ppct>
        <pages>103-114</pages>
        <tig>
          <atl>An imprisoning gaze: Practices of gendered, racialized and epistemic violence.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Pollack, Shoshana</au>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="major">Epistemology</subj>
          <subj type="major">Human Sex Differences</subj>
          <subj type="major">Racial and Ethnic Differences</subj>
          <subj type="major">Victimization</subj>
          <subj type="major">Violence</subj>
          <subj type="gender">Female</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>This article examines how correctional systems absorb feminist-inspired reformist discourses that focus upon women’s victimization as a ‘pathway’ to incarceration. Through the absorption process the concept of gender loses its socio-economic and political resonance, centering instead the psychological effects of gender oppression. A psychological notion of gender has been used to individualize and pathologize criminalized women through prison programming and is linked with notions of ‘risk’ to re-offend. I reflect upon the role of evidence-based practice (EBP) in exacerbating epistemic problems related to the subjectivity of the ‘risky victim.’ Moving beyond this conceptualization, I suggest the importance of an analysis which draws connections across spaces of confinement and challenges the very role and practices of prisons as examples of racialized and gendered violence themselves. (PsycINFO Database Record (c) 2013 APA, all rights reserved)</ab>
        <pubtype>Journal</pubtype>
        <pubtype>Peer Reviewed Journal</pubtype>
        <doctype>Journal Article</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language>English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=psyh&amp;AN=2012-35075-008&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="43">
  <header shortDbName="f3h" longDbName="Film &amp; Television Literature Index with Full Text" uiTerm="60878422">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>International Journal of Business &amp; Social Science</jtl>
        <issn>22191933</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2011" month="05" day="01">2011</dt>
        <vid>2</vid>
        <iid>8</iid>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ppf>10</ppf>
        <ppct>15</ppct>
        <formats />
        <tig>
          <atl>It's not just who you know but how well you know them: The impact of trust and relational networks in movie deal-making.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Yudelson, John</au>
          <affil>California State University Channel Islands, 1 University Drive, Camarillo, CA 93012, USA</affil>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="geo">UNITED States</subj>
          <subj type="unclass">MOTION pictures -- Production &amp; direction</subj>
          <subj type="unclass">MOTION picture producers &amp; directors</subj>
          <subj type="unclass">CONTRACTS</subj>
          <subj type="unclass">MOTION picture actors &amp; actresses</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>Deal-making requires multiple parties that can trust each other to uphold all aspects of the deal. Nowhere is this more prevalent than in Hollywood movie deals which can be in the hundreds of millions of dollars. However, not just anyone can call up a producer or studio executive with a movie idea. They must be "a player" in the network. This paper investigates how trust and networks impact how movie deals are made. It asks the question who is most central in the movie deal-making network, and how do the strength of the relationships in Hollywood impact the deal-making process? Using Centering Resonance Analysis to quantify the answers from interviews with movie deal participants, the answer of who is most central in this network - the studio executives, actors, directors, or the independent producers -- is resolved.</ab>
        <pubtype>Academic Journal</pubtype>
        <doctype>Article</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="eng">English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=f3h&amp;AN=60878422&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="44">
  <header shortDbName="psyh" longDbName="PsycINFO" uiTerm="2009-11908-001">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo>
        <btl>Perfusion imaging of the right perisylvian neural network in acute spatial neglect.</btl>
        <aug />
      </bkinfo>
      <chapinfo />
      <revinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Frontiers in Human Neuroscience</jtl>
        <issn type="Electronic">16625161</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2009" month="08" day="03">20090803</dt>
        <vid>3</vid>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ui type="doi">10.3389/neuro.09.015.2009</ui>
        <ui type="pmid">19680470</ui>
        <tig>
          <atl>Perfusion imaging of the right perisylvian neural network in acute spatial neglect.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Zopf, Regine</au>
          <au>Berger, Monika Fruhmann</au>
          <au>Klose, Uwe</au>
          <au>Karnath, Hans-Otto</au>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="major">Frontal Lobe</subj>
          <subj type="major">Parietal Lobe</subj>
          <subj type="major">Sensory Neglect</subj>
          <subj type="major">Spatial Perception</subj>
          <subj type="major">Temporal Lobe</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Magnetic Resonance Imaging</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Brain Lesions (Disorders)</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Biological Neural Networks</subj>
          <subj type="age">Adulthood (18 yrs &amp; older)</subj>
          <subj type="age">Thirties (30-39 yrs)</subj>
          <subj type="age">Aged (65 yrs &amp; older)</subj>
          <subj type="gender">Male</subj>
          <subj type="gender">Female</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>Recent studies have suggested a tightly connected perisylvian neural network associated with spatial neglect. Here we investigated whether structural damage in one part of the network typically is accompanied with functional damage in other, structurally intact areas of this network. By combining normalized fluid-attenuated inversion-recovery (FLAIR) imaging, diffusion-weighted imaging (DWI), and perfusion-weighted imaging (PWI) we asked whether or not lesions centering on fronto-temporal regions co-occur with abnormal perfusion in structurally intact parietal cortex. With thresholds applied to delineate behaviourally relevant malperfusion of brain tissue, the analysis of normalized time-to-peak (TTP) and maximal signal reduction (MSR) perfusion maps did not reveal significant changes outside the area of structural damage. In particular, we found no abnormal perfusion in the structurally intact inferior parietal lobule (IPL) and/or the temporo-parietal junction (TPJ). The present results obtained in three consecutively admitted neglect patients with fronto-temporal lesions indicate that structural damage in one part of the right perisylvian network associated with spatial neglect does not necessarily require dysfunction by malperfusion in other, structurally intact parts of the network to provoke spatial neglect. The neural tissue in the fronto-temporal cortex appears to have an original role in processes of spatial orienting and exploration. (PsycINFO Database Record (c) 2012 APA, all rights reserved)</ab>
        <pubtype>Journal</pubtype>
        <pubtype>Peer Reviewed Journal</pubtype>
        <doctype>Journal Article</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language>English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=psyh&amp;AN=2009-11908-001&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="45">
  <header shortDbName="bth" longDbName="Business Source Complete" uiTerm="95103083">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Quality Management Journal</jtl>
        <issn>10686967</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2013" month="01" day="01">2013</dt>
        <vid>20</vid>
        <iid>1</iid>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ppf>4</ppf>
        <ppct>1</ppct>
        <formats>
          <fmt type="PDF" size="36KB" />
        </formats>
        <tig>
          <atl>Introduction.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Evans, James R.</au>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="thes">TOTAL quality management</subj>
          <subj type="thes">QUALITY assurance</subj>
          <subj type="thes">MANAGEMENT research</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>An introduction is presented in which the editor discusses various reports within the issue on topics including the centering resonance analysis approach, quality management studies, and outlook for quality management research.</ab>
        <pubtype>Academic Journal</pubtype>
        <doctype>Article</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="eng">English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=bth&amp;AN=95103083&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="46">
  <header shortDbName="bth" longDbName="Business Source Complete" uiTerm="35063896">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Advances in Consumer Research</jtl>
        <issn>00989258</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2008" month="01" day="01">2008</dt>
        <vid>35</vid>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ppf>756</ppf>
        <ppct>2</ppct>
        <formats>
          <fmt type="PDF" size="66KB" />
        </formats>
        <tig>
          <atl>The Evolution of New Product Rumors in Online Consumer Communities: Social Identity or Social Impact?</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Thompson, Scott A.</au>
          <au>Ward, James C.</au>
          <affil>Arizona State University,, USA</affil>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="thes">CONSUMER behavior</subj>
          <subj type="thes">CUSTOMER satisfaction</subj>
          <subj type="thes">CUSTOMER services</subj>
          <subj type="thes">CUSTOMER relations</subj>
          <subj type="thes">ANCHORING effect</subj>
          <subj type="thes">ECONOMIC impact</subj>
          <subj type="unclass">HUMAN ecology</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>Prior studies of consumer word of mouth behavior have focused on released products. This research indicates that word of mouth serves as a complement to other sources of information such as advertising and expert reviews. However, consumers also engage in word of mouth about unconfirmed, unannounced, and unreleased products. Such rumors develop and spread in the absence of the kind of outside information present in the contexts previously studied in the word of mouth literature. Research on rumors in the social psychology literature has found that the emergence and diffusion of rumors depends on the social context and the groups involved. These results suggest that new product rumors may spread and change depending on the social context in which they exist and the interests of those spreading the rumors. Therefore, two theories of group formation and intergroup communication are considered. Social Identity Theory is the perspective adopted by the brand community literature. Social Identity Theory contends that intergroup dynamics are naturally competitive due to attempts by group members to maintain and enhance their relevant social identities through intergroup comparisons. As a result, consumer groups formed around competing products will tend to develop and spread rumors that reflect positively on their favored product and negatively on competing products. Over time, this will lead to a polarized environment with rival consumer groups either discussing completely different rumored products or discussing the same product but in different terms. This polarization should be most pronounced among the most frequent participants since they will hold the strongest social identities. On the other hand, if social identities are not as influential as the brand community literature suggests, Dynamic Social Impact Theory may be more instrumental in understanding the diffusion of new product rumors. Dynamic Social Impact Theory lacks the competitive intergroup dynamic suggested by Social Identity Theory. Instead, it suggests that the spread of new product rumors between groups will follow an iterative and assimilative process. Therefore, new product rumors should diffuse between consumer groups formed around competing products. As a result, new product rumors discussed in rival groups will become more similar over time. Furthermore, this convergence should occur more rapidly among frequent participants in each group since they are subject to the highest levels of social impact. To test these competing theories, actual word of mouth communications regarding a rumored product were gathered from three online forums. Two forums were dedicated to the products of two competing companies: Intel and AMD. In addition, messages were gathered from a third neutral "General Hardware" forum. The messages cover the period from when the first rumor about the product appeared until the non-disclosure agreement prohibiting the release of information about the product expired. The final dataset spans a period from March 2004 to July 13, 2006 and contains 409,576 messages posted from 18,121 unique user accounts. The message data was analyzed using Centering Resonance Analysis (CRA) which uses a form of network analysis grounded in centering theory. The centering theory approach employed by CRA makes it well suited to studying new product rumors. Such rumors are comprised of evolving networks of associations centering on a focal subject. Over time, these associations change as the rumor spreads between individuals and groups. CRA identifies these networks of associations and provides a method to measure both the relationships and the degree to which networks vary between texts. Therefore, CRA provides a means to assess whether rumors are growing more or less similar and more or less focal within and across the three forums. The results show that new product rumors become more similar between the rival consumer forums over time.…</ab>
        <pubtype>Academic Journal</pubtype>
        <doctype>Article</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="eng">English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=bth&amp;AN=35063896&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="47">
  <header shortDbName="bth" longDbName="Business Source Complete" uiTerm="9330658">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Human Systems Management</jtl>
        <issn>01672533</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2002" month="12" day="01">2002</dt>
        <vid>21</vid>
        <iid>4</iid>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ppf>217</ppf>
        <ppct>12</ppct>
        <formats>
          <fmt type="PDF" size="170KB" />
        </formats>
        <tig>
          <atl>A knowledge directory for identifying experts and areas of expertise.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Dooley, Kevin J.</au>
          <au>Corman, Steven R.</au>
          <au>McPhee, Robert D.</au>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="thes">KNOWLEDGE management</subj>
          <subj type="thes">ORGANIZATIONAL learning</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>Individuals in organizations often need to access knowledge that is outside their own area of expertise. Doing so requires "know-who" knowledge-knowledge of who knows what inside (or outside) the organization. This paper develops the concept of a knowledge directory, a database that can be searched via query. The knowledge directory returns a list of individuals rank ordered by the mutual affinity between their own areas of expertise and the content of the query. The technology behind the matching of person and query is centering resonance analysis, which develops a knowledge map, representing objects embedded in text as a network graph. We also present a way to analyze a collection of knowledge maps so that clusters of people who have similar expertise may be identified. We apply these techniques to a group of ten university faculty from the areas of industrial engineering, operations management, and supply chain management. Experiments attempting to match queries to specific faculty members are presented and discussed, and clustering techniques are used to show how the faculty aggregate into cliques of similar content and methodological expertise. Extensions of the method are discussed.</ab>
        <pubtype>Academic Journal</pubtype>
        <doctype>Article</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="eng">English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=bth&amp;AN=9330658&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="48">
  <header shortDbName="psyh" longDbName="PsycINFO" uiTerm="2010-12079-001">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo>
        <btl>The leader as the face of a crisis: Philip Morris' CEO's speeches during the 1990s.</btl>
        <aug />
      </bkinfo>
      <chapinfo />
      <revinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Journal of Public Relations Research</jtl>
        <issn type="Print">1062726X</issn>
        <issn type="Electronic">1532754X</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2009" month="10" day="01">20091001</dt>
        <vid>21</vid>
        <iid>4</iid>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ui type="doi">10.1080/10627260902966425</ui>
        <ppct>20</ppct>
        <pages>361-380</pages>
        <tig>
          <atl>The leader as the face of a crisis: Philip Morris' CEO's speeches during the 1990s.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>de Fatima Oliveira, Maria</au>
          <au>Murphy, Priscilla</au>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="major">Business and Industrial Personnel</subj>
          <subj type="major">Management Methods</subj>
          <subj type="major">Organizational Crises</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Public Speaking</subj>
          <subj type="age">Adulthood (18 yrs &amp; older)</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>This research investigated Philip Morris’ crisis communication management strategies during the 1990s through the study of its CEO’s speeches. This analysis explored the company’s maneuvers to camouflage controversies in acceptable social expectations. Pairing framing theory with centering resonance analysis, this research found 3 distinct frames: profitable multinational (1994–1996), litigation target (1997–1998), and corporate good citizen (1999–2001). Avoidance of talk about health issues indicated the company’s strategic adaptation to a shifting legal and public opinion climate, as it sought to authenticate its right to do business by reframing the notion of corporate responsibility away from healthy products and toward high-price philanthropy. (PsycINFO Database Record (c) 2012 APA, all rights reserved)</ab>
        <pubtype>Journal</pubtype>
        <pubtype>Peer Reviewed Journal</pubtype>
        <doctype>Journal Article</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language>English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=psyh&amp;AN=2010-12079-001&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="49">
  <header shortDbName="a9h" longDbName="Academic Search Complete" uiTerm="25594767">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>COMPEL</jtl>
        <issn>03321649</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2007" month="06" day="19">2007</dt>
        <vid>26</vid>
        <iid>3</iid>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ppf>800</ppf>
        <ppct>14</ppct>
        <formats />
        <tig>
          <atl>Design of an electromagnetic actuator for parametric stiffness excitation.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Erich Schmidt</au>
          <au>Wolfgang Paradeiser</au>
          <au>Fadi Dohnal</au>
          <au>Horst Ecker</au>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="thes">ACTUATORS</subj>
          <subj type="thes">ELECTROMAGNETIC devices</subj>
          <subj type="thes">DESIGN</subj>
          <subj type="thes">MATHEMATICAL models</subj>
          <subj type="thes">FINITE element method</subj>
          <subj type="naics">Fluid Power Cylinder and Actuator Manufacturing</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>Purpose - An overview is given on design features, numerical modelling and testing of a novel electromagnetic actuator to achieve a controllable stiffness to be used as a device for parametric stiffness excitation. Design/methodology/approach - In principle, the actuator consists of a current driven coil placed between two permanent magnets. Repellent forces are generated between the coil and the magnets, centering the coil between the two magnets. The 2D finite element analyses are carried out to predict the forces generated by this arrangement depending on coil current and coil position. Force measurements are also made using the actual device. Findings - Actuator forces as predicted by the finite element analyses are in excellent agreement with the measured data, confirming the validity of the numerical model. Stiffness of the actuator is defined as the increase of force per unit of coil displacement. Actuator stiffness depends linearly on the coil current but in a nonlinear manner on the coil displacement. The performance of the actuator is sufficient to demonstrate the effect of a so-called parametric anti-resonance on a test stand. Research limitations/implications - Although the performance of the actuator is satisfactory, there is potential for further improvement of the actuator design. Originality/value - This paper reports for the first time on an electromechanical device to create a time-periodic stiffness variation to be used for research in the field of parametrically excited mechanical systems. The device is used to prove experimentally an effect to suppress mechanical vibrations which has been studied so far only in theoretical studies.</ab>
        <pubtype>Academic Journal</pubtype>
        <doctype>Article</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="eng">English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=a9h&amp;AN=25594767&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="50">
  <header shortDbName="psyh" longDbName="PsycINFO" uiTerm="2010-04533-014">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo>
        <btl>From 7/7 to 8/10: Media framing of terrorist incidents in the United States and United Kingdom.</btl>
        <aug>
          <au type="editor">Canter, David</au>
        </aug>
        <isbn type="Paperback">9780470753811</isbn>
        <isbn type="Hardcover">9780470753804</isbn>
      </bkinfo>
      <chapinfo />
      <revinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>The faces of terrorism: Multidisciplinary perspectives.</jtl>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2009" month="01" day="01">20090101</dt>
        <place>Hoboken, NJ</place>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ppct>18</ppct>
        <pages>227-244</pages>
        <tig>
          <atl>From 7/7 to 8/10: Media framing of terrorist incidents in the United States and United Kingdom.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Brinson, Mary</au>
          <au>Stohl, Michael</au>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="major">Communications Media</subj>
          <subj type="major">Mass Media</subj>
          <subj type="major">Newspapers</subj>
          <subj type="major">Terrorism</subj>
          <subj type="major">Violence</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>Communication and media are as important to the terrorist and the government as the actual act of violence itself. Therefore analysis of news coverage and its implications are crucial for counterterrorism efforts. This paper consequently explores media framing of terrorist incidents and patterns of indexing in both the United States and United Kingdom. The study looks at several newspapers within these countries from the years of 2005 and 2006. Specifically, it investigates coverage during this time period concerning both the 7/7/05 London bombings and the 08/10/06 transatlantic terror plot. The study employs CRA (Centering Resonance Analysis) to evaluate the frames chosen to present the incidents in British and American media. The content analysis findings are extended to actual political elite statements and opinions in an effort to support Bennett's indexing theory and further it to a context of framing and terrorism. (PsycINFO Database Record (c) 2012 APA, all rights reserved)</ab>
        <pubtype>Book</pubtype>
        <pubtype>Edited Book</pubtype>
        <doctype>Chapter</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language>English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=psyh&amp;AN=2010-04533-014&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="51">
  <header shortDbName="a9h" longDbName="Academic Search Complete" uiTerm="47762337">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo />
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Medical Physics</jtl>
        <issn>00942405</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2010" month="02" day="01">Feb2010</dt>
        <vid>37</vid>
        <iid>2</iid>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ui type="doi">10.1118/1.3298019</ui>
        <ppf>877</ppf>
        <ppct>8</ppct>
        <formats />
        <tig>
          <atl>Susceptibility gradient quantization by MRI signal response mapping (SIRMA) to dephaser.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Franconi, F.</au>
          <au>Chapon, C.</au>
          <au>Le Jeune, J. J.</au>
          <au>Richomme, P.</au>
          <au>Lemaire, L.</au>
          <affil>Plateforme d'Ingénierie et d'Analyses Moléculaires, Université d'Angers, 45045 Angers, France</affil>
          <affil>INSERM U 646, "Ingénierie de la Vectorisation," Université d'Angers, 49100 Angers, France.</affil>
          <affil>Université d'Angers, UMR-S 646, 49100 Angers, France</affil>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="thes">MAGNETIC resonance imaging</subj>
          <subj type="thes">IMAGING systems in medicine</subj>
          <subj type="thes">DIAGNOSTIC imaging</subj>
          <subj type="thes">METALLIC oxides</subj>
          <subj type="thes">MAGNETIC resonance</subj>
          <subj type="naics">Other Electronic and Precision Equipment Repair and Maintenance</subj>
          <subj type="naics">Diagnostic Imaging Centers</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>Purpose: Susceptibility effects are a very efficient source of contrast in magnetic resonance imaging. However, detection is hampered by the fact the induced contrast is negative. In this work, the SIgnal Response MApping (SIRMA) to dephaser method is proposed to map susceptibility gradient to improve visualization. Methods: In conventional gradient echo acquisitions, the echo formation of susceptibility affected spins is shifted in k-space, the shift being proportional to the susceptibility gradient. Susceptibility gradients map can be produced by measuring this induced shifts. The SIRMA method measures these shifts from a series of dephased images collected with additional incremental dephasers. These additional dephasers correspond either to a slice refocusing gradient offset or to a reconstruction window off-centering. The signal intensity profile as a function of the additional dephaser was determined on a pixel-by-pixel basis from the ensemble of dephased images. Susceptibility affected voxels presented a signal response profile maximum shifted compared to nonaffected voxels ones. Shift magnitude and sign were measured for each pixel to determine susceptibility gradients and produce a susceptibility gradient map. Results: In vitro experiments demonstrated the ability of the method to map gradient inhomogeneities induced by a cylinder. Quantization accuracy was evaluated comparing SIRMA images and simulations performed on the well-characterized air filled cylinder model. Performances of the SIRMA method, evaluated in vitro on cylinders filled with various superparamagnetic iron oxide SPIO concentrations, showed limited influence of acquisition parameters. Robustness of the method was then assessed in vivo after an infusion of SPIO-loaded nanocapsules into the rat brain using a convection-enhanced drug delivery approach. The region of massive susceptibility gradient induced by the SPIO-loaded nanocapsules was clearly delineated on SIRMA maps and images were compared to T2* weighted images, Susceptibility Gradient Map (SGM), and histological Perl’s staining slice. The potential for quantitative evaluation of SPIO distribution volume was demonstrated. Conclusions: The proposed method is a promising technique for a wide range of applications especially in molecular or cellular imaging with respect to its quantitative nature and its computational simplicity.</ab>
        <pubtype>Academic Journal</pubtype>
        <doctype>Article</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language code="eng">English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=a9h&amp;AN=47762337&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="52">
  <header shortDbName="psyh" longDbName="PsycINFO" uiTerm="2011-99030-573">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo>
        <btl>Credibility in the blogosphere: A study of measurement and influence of wine blogs as an information source.</btl>
        <aug />
        <isbn>9781124123660</isbn>
      </bkinfo>
      <chapinfo />
      <revinfo />
      <dissinfo>
        <disstl>Credibility in the blogosphere: A study of measurement and influence of wine blogs as an information source.</disstl>
      </dissinfo>
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Dissertation Abstracts International Section A: Humanities and Social Sciences</jtl>
        <issn type="Print">04194209</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2011" month="01" day="01">20110101</dt>
        <vid>71</vid>
        <iid>8-A</iid>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ui type="umi">AAI3416098</ui>
        <ppct>1</ppct>
        <pages>2963-2963</pages>
        <tig>
          <atl>Credibility in the blogosphere: A study of measurement and influence of wine blogs as an information source.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Rickman, Tracy A.</au>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="major">Credibility</subj>
          <subj type="major">Information</subj>
          <subj type="major">Internet</subj>
          <subj type="major">Measurement</subj>
          <subj type="major">Wine</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Persuasive Communication</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>The use of online sources for decision information continues to grow among wine consumers. One of these sources is the wine blog, a venue for user-generated content that simulates word-of-mouth (WOM) communication. The growth and influence of wine blogs creates opportunities for wine marketers to use them as part of strategy development. To facilitate an understanding of wine blogs and their potential influence on consumers‘ decisions, a conceptual model of the influence of wine blog credibility was proposed. Within this model, this dissertation examined the influence of the credibility of wine blogs on wine blog readers‘ behavioral intentions (e.g., purchase), as mediated by trust and moderated by involvement. The appraisal of wine blog credibility was characterized as tri-dimensional – assessed by characteristics of site, message, and source. The purpose of this research was to develop credibility scales for wine blogs (site, message, and source) and test the influence of a wine blog‘s credibility on wine consumers‘ behavioral intentions. Phase 1 implemented online focus groups to gather characteristics of the wine blog that signal credibility to the reader. Centering resonance analysis was used to generate items for scale development. Phase 2 used online survey data to validate the proposed scales and test the influence of a wine blog‘s credibility on a reader‘s intentions as specified in the model. The research findings revealed that although all three credibility dimensions demonstrated a positive relationship and statistical significance with wine blog trust attitude, only source credibility indicated practical significance. In addition, the data supported the hypothesized influence of wine blog credibility on the intention to follow recommendations and to continue blog participation as mediated by trust. However, the findings indicated that source credibility was the main contributor to the proportion of variance in both intentions. Furthermore, the data did not fully support the central versus peripheral routes hypothesized according to the elaboration likelihood model (ELM). The hypothesized peripheral route of source assessment on trust was predictive for individuals with both levels of involvement and substantively more predictive than either of the other two dimensions (site assessment as peripheral route, message assessment as central route). (PsycINFO Database Record (c) 2012 APA, all rights reserved)</ab>
        <pubtype>Dissertation Abstract</pubtype>
        <doctype>Dissertation</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language>English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=psyh&amp;AN=2011-99030-573&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="53">
  <header shortDbName="psyh" longDbName="PsycINFO" uiTerm="2009-99230-498">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo>
        <btl>The ball is in their court: Changing role of multinational companies from emerging nations.</btl>
        <aug />
        <isbn>9781109215083</isbn>
      </bkinfo>
      <chapinfo />
      <revinfo />
      <dissinfo>
        <disstl>The ball is in their court: Changing role of multinational companies from emerging nations.</disstl>
      </dissinfo>
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Dissertation Abstracts International Section A: Humanities and Social Sciences</jtl>
        <issn type="Print">04194209</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2009" month="01" day="01">20090101</dt>
        <vid>70</vid>
        <iid>6-A</iid>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ui type="umi">AAI3359670</ui>
        <ppct>1</ppct>
        <pages>2133-2133</pages>
        <tig>
          <atl>The ball is in their court: Changing role of multinational companies from emerging nations.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Kothari, Tanvi H.</au>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="major">Adjudication</subj>
          <subj type="major">Business Organizations</subj>
          <subj type="major">Competition</subj>
          <subj type="major">Multinational Corporations</subj>
          <subj type="major">Organizational Behavior</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Globalization</subj>
          <subj type="age">Adulthood (18 yrs &amp; older)</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>One of the emerging phenomena of global competition is the increasing participation of firms from emerging economies in various industries and across value chain activities. These MNCs from developing and emerging economies have recently shown an unprecedented increase in numbers (from only 19 firms in 1990 featured in the Fortune 500 list to 47 in 2005) (UNCTAD, 2006). While these Emerging Nation Multinational Companies (EMCs) are gaining a strong foothold in the global economy, some evidence also suggests that their foreign direct investments are being targeted towards advanced economies in both resource industries and higher-value adding activities. On the face of it, the disadvantages of being a late entrant seem overwhelming and based on the stages model of internationalization the EMCs may not be able to compete against global giants whose dominance is rooted in their first-mover status (Bartlett &amp; Goshal, 2000). However, the success of EMCs like the Tata Motors, Lenovo, and the like raise an important research issue as to what are the strategies these EMCs pursue as they begin to compete in the global competitive landscape? In the past, scholars have conducted substantial research on internationalization, Multinational Companies (MNCs), and Foreign Direct Investment (FDI) which explain the behavior of first-mover MNCs from developed countries based on technological superiority. Those theories were developed within a specific environmental context and do an adequate job to explain a fairly specific set of observed firm behaviors. Each, within its context, may be fairly adequate at explaining those behaviors. However, the emergence of EMCs in the global economic environment highlights that times have changed and the incumbent MNCs (studied earlier) constantly face threats from these emerging giants. As the context changes, so has the ability of the prior internationalization theories to explain behaviors observed in this global economy diminished considerably. Lately, a few researchers have started a new line of research to uncover some distinct characteristics of these EMCs. However, very little is known about the foreign expansion strategies of these EMCs and warrants a need to explore this phenomenon indepth. In order to bridge this gap in the literature this dissertation uses an inductive approach by conducting multiple case-studies to understand the foreign expansion strategies of sixteen companies that originate from two key emerging nations: India and China. This exploratory approach supported by computerized content analysis of longitudinal text data allows us to observe the significance of specific constructs, begin to detect patterns and regularities in the behavior of EMCs and compare EMCs originating from various emerging nations. Methodologically, the dissertation illustrates the usefulness of semantic network analysis tools, especially centering resonance analysis, in identifying and interpreting the concepts that provide coherence to set of textual data. Further, using factor analysis we identify some key themes that explain the foreign expansion strategies of these EMCs. The results of this study suggest that EMCs’ expansion is, on one hand, based on their ability to acquire resources and absorb them to build their own advantage (supply side dynamics). On the other hand, it is also based on EMCs’ ability to find some market niches, i.e., entering into markets untapped by traditional MNCs (demand side dynamics). Finally, based on our analysis of these in-depth case-studies we identify some propositions as anchors for further theory building. Specifically, we identify three major anchors, namely, EMCs’ ability to ‘Lick the Dirt’; ‘Cash Rich Positions of EMCs’ and ‘Strategic Partnerships with Developed Country Firms’ that enhance their  ‘Competitive Advantage in Developed Nations. (PsycINFO Database Record (c) 2012 APA, all rights reserved)</ab>
        <pubtype>Dissertation Abstract</pubtype>
        <doctype>Dissertation</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language>English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=psyh&amp;AN=2009-99230-498&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="54">
  <header shortDbName="psyh" longDbName="PsycINFO" uiTerm="2007-99190-678">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo>
        <btl>Listen to what i have to say: An exploration of what high school students perceive they need in order to be successful in school.</btl>
        <aug />
      </bkinfo>
      <chapinfo />
      <revinfo />
      <dissinfo>
        <disstl>Listen to what i have to say: An exploration of what high school students perceive they need in order to be successful in school.</disstl>
      </dissinfo>
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Dissertation Abstracts International Section A: Humanities and Social Sciences</jtl>
        <issn type="Print">04194209</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2007" month="01" day="01">20070101</dt>
        <vid>68</vid>
        <iid>4-A</iid>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ui type="umi">AAI3263297</ui>
        <ppct>1</ppct>
        <pages>1314-1314</pages>
        <tig>
          <atl>Listen to what i have to say: An exploration of what high school students perceive they need in order to be successful in school.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Votteler, Nancy Kay Blackmon</au>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="major">Academic Achievement</subj>
          <subj type="major">High School Students</subj>
          <subj type="major">School Environment</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Psychoanalysts</subj>
          <subj type="age">Adolescence (13-17 yrs)</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>Students speak out about what they perceive they need to be successful in school in this comparative case study. Using survey methods and qualitative procedures, the researcher examined experiences of specific individuals in natural settings from multiple perspectives. Students from two large urban schools participated in the Students as Allies survey, underwritten by the What Kids Can Do Organization and MetLife Foundation, designed to elicit responses about school safety, school climate, teachers, administrators and other factors supporting student success. In addition to the survey, students read and discussed the book Fires in the Bathroom by Kathleen Cushman. Students wrote their reflections about the content of the book as well as reflections on class discussions. Data were collected over three months, and source data included survey, on-site observations and student written responses. The analyst viewed survey open-essay questions and journal responses in regards to theories on writing to learn (Britton, 1970; Emig, 1977; Murray, 1996), conversation and discourse analysis (Bakhtin, 1981; Gee, 1992), sociocultural theory (Bruner, 1968; Vygotsky, 1978), student engagement (Deci, 1972; Csikszentmihalyi, 1991), student voice (Cushman, 2003; Fielding, 2004, Mitra, 2003), school climate factors (Freiberg, 1999; Hoy &amp; Miskel), and caring pedagogy (hooks, 2000; Noddings, 2002). Survey questions were then analyzed, and patterns began to emerge as questions about "self," "student," "others," and "teachers." The written responses were analyzed using Centering Resonance Analysis, a computerized text analysis based on centering theory in linguistics. Patterns emerged from the student writing as "core of self," "others," and "fruitfulness" (Gee, 2001, Del-Castillo, 2004). The study revealed what students say they need from teachers and school administrators in order to be successful in school: caring and competent teachers, more engaging classes and class work, class time to talk about the work, and school climate factors that motivate students to learn. Implications for practice and recommendations for further study were provided. (PsycINFO Database Record (c) 2012 APA, all rights reserved)</ab>
        <pubtype>Dissertation Abstract</pubtype>
        <doctype>Dissertation</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language>English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=psyh&amp;AN=2007-99190-678&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="55">
  <header shortDbName="pdh" longDbName="PsycARTICLES" uiTerm="2005-14234-003">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo>
        <btl>Review of The integration of behavior.</btl>
        <aug>
          <au type="bkauth">French, Thomas M.</au>
        </aug>
      </bkinfo>
      <chapinfo />
      <revinfo>
        <rtl>The integration of behavior</rtl>
        <aug>
          <au type="reviewer">Hanfmann, Eugenia</au>
        </aug>
      </revinfo>
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>The Journal of Abnormal and Social Psychology</jtl>
        <issn type="Print">0096851X</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="1955" month="03" day="01">19550301</dt>
        <vid>50</vid>
        <iid>2</iid>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ui type="doi">10.1037/h0038601</ui>
        <ppct>4</ppct>
        <pages>279-282</pages>
        <formats>
          <fmt type="PDF" size="454KB" />
        </formats>
        <tig>
          <atl>Review of The integration of behavior.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Hanfmann, Eugenia</au>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="major">Behavior</subj>
          <subj type="major">Dreaming</subj>
          <subj type="major">Personality Theory</subj>
          <subj type="major">Psychoanalytic Theory</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>Reviews the book, The integration of behavior by Thomas M. French (1952). In this fundamental contribution to Ego psychology French undertakes to elucidate the workings of integrative mechanisms, using as illustrative material the record of the analysis of an asthmatic patient. The first volume--Basic Postulates (see record [rid]1952-05902-000[/rid]) presnts, in a first approximation, the conceptual framework evolved by French, exemplifying the "basic postulates" by instances taken from everyday normal behavior and from some of the patient's dreams. In the second volume--The Integrative Process in Dreams (see record [rid]1954-05671-000[/rid]) the author brings detailed analyses of several sequences of the patient's dreams, elaborating the integrative processes and the system of personal patterns reflected in these dreams. French's undertaking can be considered as one of the most valuable among the current attempts to evolve a systematic "ego psychology," centering it on the successfully integrated behavior, on constructive, rather than defensive, functions of the psychic organization. Through a judicious selection of concepts and theories that have both a high explanatory power and a close fit to facts, he tries to "bring into resonance" not only the rational and irrational behavior, but also many other dichotomous areas and approaches of the personality study. Personality psychologists will certainly welcome this attempt at overcoming the segregation of various approaches to the study of human behavior, even if one may disagree with the specific selections French makes, and regret the fact that the inclusion of so many theories and speculations tends to obliterate the main outlines of the work. (PsycINFO Database Record (c) 2013 APA, all rights reserved)</ab>
        <pubtype>Journal</pubtype>
        <pubtype>Peer Reviewed Journal</pubtype>
        <doctype>Review-Book</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language>English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=pdh&amp;AN=2005-14234-003&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec>
<rec resultID="56">
  <header shortDbName="psyh" longDbName="PsycINFO" uiTerm="2009-99070-040">
    <controlInfo>
      <bkinfo>
        <btl>Diversity of thought in the blogosphere: Implications for influencing and monitoring image.</btl>
        <aug />
        <isbn>9780549863199</isbn>
      </bkinfo>
      <chapinfo />
      <revinfo />
      <dissinfo>
        <disstl>Diversity of thought in the blogosphere: Implications for influencing and monitoring image.</disstl>
      </dissinfo>
      <jinfo>
        <jtl>Dissertation Abstracts International Section A: Humanities and Social Sciences</jtl>
        <issn type="Print">04194209</issn>
      </jinfo>
      <pubinfo>
        <dt year="2009" month="01" day="01">20090101</dt>
        <vid>69</vid>
        <iid>10-A</iid>
      </pubinfo>
      <artinfo>
        <ui type="umi">AAI3333655</ui>
        <ppct>1</ppct>
        <pages>4038-4038</pages>
        <tig>
          <atl>Diversity of thought in the blogosphere: Implications for influencing and monitoring image.</atl>
        </tig>
        <aug>
          <au>Dwyer, Paul</au>
        </aug>
        <sug>
          <subj type="major">Consumer Attitudes</subj>
          <subj type="major">Monitoring</subj>
          <subj type="major">Social Psychology</subj>
          <subj type="major">Computer Mediated Communication</subj>
          <subj type="major">Websites</subj>
          <subj type="minor">Business Organizations</subj>
        </sug>
        <ab>A blog, a shortened form of weblog, is a website where an author shares thoughts in posts or entries. Most blogs permit readers to add comments to posts and thereby be a conversational mechanism. One way that companies have started to use blogs is to monitor their corporate image (in this dissertation, the term image is used in reference to corporate, brand and/or product image). This study focuses on how common socio-psychological processes mediate consumers’ revelation of corporate image in the blogosphere. Centering resonance analysis, a means of measuring similarity between two bodies of text, is used in conjunction with multidimensional scaling to locate text as cognitive objects in a space. Clusters are then detected and measured to quantify diversity in the thoughts expressed. Detected patterns are studied from a social process theory perspective, where complex phenomena are hypothesized to be the result of the interaction of simpler processes. A majority of blog commenters compromise the expression of their thoughts to gain social acceptance. This study identifies the most extreme of such people so companies who monitor blogs can assign less weight to image indications gained from them as they may be merely expressing thoughts that are intended to maintain social acceptance. It was also found that single-theme blogs attract a readership with similarly narrow interests. The boldest and most diverse thinkers among comment writers have the most impact because of their ability to provoke the thinking of others. However, commenters who repeat the same ideas have little effect, suggesting that introducing shills is unlikely to shift the sentiment of a blog's readership. People participate in blog communities for reasons (e.g., need for community) that may undermine thought diversity. However, there may be value in serving those needs even though no valuable insights are provided into image or directions for product development. Members of homogeneous-thinking communities were observed to more actively participate, with greater longevity. This may increase loyalty to the company hosting the blog. (PsycINFO Database Record (c) 2012 APA, all rights reserved)</ab>
        <pubtype>Dissertation Abstract</pubtype>
        <doctype>Dissertation</doctype>
      </artinfo>
      <language>English</language>
    </controlInfo>
    <displayInfo>
      <pLink>
        <url>http://search.ebscohost.com/login.aspx?direct=true&amp;db=psyh&amp;AN=2009-99070-040&amp;site=ehost-live</url>
      </pLink>
    </displayInfo>
  </header>
</rec></records>